哈特, 你能给我亚利桑那的号码吗?
Hart, can you get me Miss Arizona's number?
我为什么要这样做呢, 克隆斯基?
Why would I do that, Clonsky?
因为她的生活中需要一个男人
Because she needs a man in her life.
是吗? 你哪里适合啦?
Yeah? Where do you fit in?
- 好,很好的对话, 不是很适意, 哈特  - 是的
-Nice. Nice talk. Not too congenial, Hart.  -Yeah.
这上面说你看上去真的很和蔼
It says right here you're supposed to be real amiable.
那是三星期前了 自从...以后我就很和蔼
That's three weeks ago. I've been amiable since then...
...不过现在我只想踹某人
...and now I just wanna hit somebody.
好吧, 你的机会来了, 哈特
Well, this could be your chance, Hart.
好的, 让我们再复习一下 家庭主妇们...
Okay, let's go over this one more time. The Housewives...
...她们在一个月内抢了九家银行 伤了两个警卫
...they knocked off nine banks in a month and wounded two guards.
我们得到线报这家银行是她们的下一个目标
We got a tip this bank is their next target
所以保持冷静, 提高警惕
So stay frosty. Keep your heads up.
在这次行动中你不能穿泳衣 你明白的, 是吗, 哈特?
You know you can't wear a swimsuit on this mission, right, Hart?
那很好
That's good.
- 世界和平怎么了?  - 它总是来来去去的
-What happened to world peace?  -It comes and goes.
大妈妈调试
Control to Big Mama.
检查你的孩子
Check your baby.
嗨, 甜心
Hey, honey.
- 调试, 大妈妈, 确认  - 确认, 大妈妈, 继续
-Control, this is Big Mama. Confirm.  -Confirm, Big Mama. Proceed on in.
- 大爸爸和大妈妈进去了  - 复制
-Big Daddy and Big Mama are inside.  -Copy that.
我希望能早点结束 我今晚还有杨李的票子呐
I hope we wrap this early. I have Yankee tickets tonight.
你在干吗?
What are you up to?
只是基本的文书工作 然后去公司吃晚饭...
Just basic paperwork, and then I got company coming over for dinner...
...所以我只需要一点... 一点解冻
...so I just need to do a little... A little defrosting.
- 哦,你的男朋友艾瑞克也过来吗?  -他不是我的男朋友, 只是...
-Oh, your boyfriend Eric's coming over?  -He's not my boyfriend. Just...
我们只是朋友, 你明白吗? 朋友和拍档, 很好的拍档
We're just friends, you know? Friends and coworkers. Friendly coworkers.
嗨, 你曾在波科诺斯?
Hey, you ever been to the Poconos?
在哪? 那是什么, 纽约? 宾夕法尼亚?
Where is that? What is that, New York? Pennsylvania?
你认为在那预定困难吗?
You think it'd be hard to get a reservation there?
什么, 你和你的拍档要去?
What, for you and your coworker?
- 那很甜蜜, 两个探员陷入爱河  - 是的
-That's so sweet, two agents in love.  -Yeah.
所以我认为这是个很好的时机告诉你 这不是你的孩子
So I guess this is a good time to tell you that this is not your baby.
家庭主妇们, 前门, 家庭主妇们
Housewives, front door. Housewives.
几岁了?
How old?
- 35  - 不, 指的是孩子, 我能看看吗?
-Thirty-five.  -No, the baby. Can I take a peek?
不, 走开, 女生 我们一个星期没给它换尿布了
No, get lost, lady. We haven't changed his diaper in a week.
你是那个最具亲和力小姐
You're that Miss Congeniality lady.
不, 我不是, 我不是, 我不是
No, I'm not. I'm not. I'm not.
我在电视上看见过你 美国小姐庆典
I saw you on TV on the Miss United States pageant.
不, 女生, 女士, 你认错人了
No, ma'am. Ma'am, you did not.
- 你是格雷西 哈特!  - 女士, 不, 女士, 请别...
-You're Gracie Hart!  -Ma'am, no. Ma'am, please...
- 格雷西 哈特! - 格雷西 哈特!
-Gracie Hart?  -Gracie Hart?
- 格雷西 哈特?  - 不, 我不是! 不是! 我不是!
-Gracie Hart!  -No, I'm not! I'm not! I'm not!
- 她是FBI!  - 我不是!
-She's FBl!  -I'm not!
- 这是抢劫!  - 好的, 谁都不许动! 不许动!
-It's a setup!  -Okay, nobody move! Nobody move!
- 大家都别动, 女生, 请...
Nobody's moving. Ma'am, please be...
请安静! 蹲下! 不许动
Please be quiet! Get down! Nobody's moving.
- 蹲下, 请! 请, 蹲下!  - 蹲下, 我说, 蹲下!
-Get down, please! Please, get down!  -Down, I said. Down!
大家都别动, 没事 女士, 蹲下! 蹲下!
Nobody's moving. It's okay. Ma'am, get down! Get down!
我们有人质危机 我们需要增援, 现在!
We've got a hostage situation. We need backup. Now!
- 我们走了, 女士们!  - 好的, 好的, 没事
-We gotta move, ladies!  -Okay. Okay, it's okay.
把你的手从钱包那拿开, 哈特
Get your hand out of the purse, Hart.
你也是, 丈夫, 举起你的手 放到我能看见的地方
You too, hubby, get your hands up where I can see them.
告诉我还有多少探员在这个银行
Tell me where every other agent is in this bank.
现在
Now.
现在!
Now!
在婴儿车里还有一个
There's one in the baby carriage.
- 别动, FBI!  - FBI, 别动!
-Freeze, FBl!  -FBl, freeze!
把枪放下! 把枪放下!
Put the gun down! Put the guns down!
- 按住她, 按住...  - 抓住了
-Take her. Take...  -Got her.
克隆斯基, 你被射中哪里了? 射中哪里?
Clonsky, where are you hit? Where are you hit?
- 射中防弹衣, 我...  - 哪里?
-In the vest. I'm...  -Where?
我没事, 没事
I'm all right. I'm all right.
- 哦, 上帝  - 那像妈妈一样疼
-Oh, my God.  -It hurt like a mother.
我知道
I know.
我来找找什么能使你好受些
But I got something that's gonna make you feel a lot better.
这就是, 602 -555 -01 99
Here we go, 602 -555 -01 99.
那是什么?
What's that?
亚利桑那小姐的电话号码
Miss Arizona's number.
- 你就不能早点告诉我?  - 不
-You couldn't tell me earlier?  -No.
- 需要什么吗?  - 我没事
-What do we got?  -I'm okay.
抱歉
Excuse me.
你介意吗?
Would you mind?
哈特! 哈特!
Hart! Hart!
- 抱歉, 长官  - 有更糟的消息
-Sorry, sir.  -Let's not make a bad day worse.
长官...
Sir...
...关于银行, 我不知道发生了什么
...about the bank, I don't know what happened.
这就像是我的高中聚会 除了这些人都喜欢我
It was like my high school reunion, except these people liked me.
是的, 我认为我们都能够同意 按照计划这不会发生
Well, I think we can all agree it didn't go according to plan.
但是我要和你说的是另外一些事
But I wanna talk to you about something else.
自从庆典以后我们收到了 好多你的粉丝的邮件
This is some fan mail we've gotten for you since the pageant.
信件, 卡片, 巧克力
Letters, cards, chocolates.
我想要巧克力
I'll take the chocolates.
"亲爱的哈特小姐, 我在庆典上看见你...
"Dear Miss Hart, I saw you on the pageant...
...第二天晚上我去出席一个聚会...
...and the next night I was coming out of a party...
...就在那是有个可怕的家伙 在停车场抢劫了我
...when this horrible guy grabbed me in the parking lot.
所以我用了你的"SING"防卫措施 然后他就逃跑了
So I did your SlNG self -defense, and he totally backed off.
之后我还经历了许多困难的事情 你很难想像这意味着什么...
I've gone through some tough times lately, and you have no idea what it means...
...我总是感觉你又站在了我的背后
...to feel like you can stand up for yourself again.
我只是想和你说声谢谢 你看上去很美在你穿...
I just wanted to say thank you and you look beautiful in your e..."
- 晚礼服?  - 晚礼服
-Evening gown?  -Evening gown.
- 她喜欢这个?  - 罗莉, 纽瓦克
-She liked it?  -Lori, Newark.
长官, 你读了我的邮件 这是B等错误
Sir, you're reading my mail. That's a class -B misdemeanor.
哈特, 我每天都要接到五个电话 要你去参加脱口秀
Hart, I've been getting five calls a day for you to be on talk shows.
最近总局的公众形象不太好...
The Bureau's had some bad publicity lately...
...头希望你能够成为FBI的新形象代言
...and the director thinks you could be the new face of the FBl.
长官, 我只是一名探员
Sir, I'm just a field agent.
绝大多数探员是不会在家 接到总统的祝贺电话的
Most field agents don't have the president calling them at home to congratulate them.
我不能相信我挂了他的电话 我本来以为是克隆斯基的
I can't believe I hung up on him. I thought it was Clonsky.
这是很重要的, 哈特 回家, 吃顿好的晚餐...
This is important, Hart. Go home, have a nice dinner...
...然后仔细考虑一下
...and think about it.
好吧...
Well...
...我会吃顿好的, 长官
...I could use a nice dinner, sir.
我也会仔细考虑的
I'll think about it.
哈特
Hart.
哦, 你好, 我是马休斯探员
Well, hello, Agent Matthews.
不, 我只是把最后一笔 放在你的鸡肉饼里
No, I'm just putting the finishing touches on your chicken potpie. Yeah.
我想总有一天我 会使某人非常, 非常幸福
I think I'm gonna make some man very, very happy someday.
听着, 我想要问你点事
Listen, I wanna ask you something.
你知道波科诺斯是否在在纽约 或者是宾夕法尼亚?
Do you know if the Poconos are in New York or Pennsylvania?
因为我对这个问题 没能找到明确的答案
Because I cannot seem to get a clear answer on this.
因为我在想, 也许这个周末...
Because I was thinking that maybe this weekend...
...我们可以开车过去 做个探险, 做...
...we could take a little drive down there, do a little exploring, do...
为什么不...?
Why, aren't...?
你为什么想要明天谈呢? 我的意思是, 你不能10分钟内过来吗?
Why do you wanna talk tomorrow? I mean, aren't you gonna be here in 1 0 minutes?
哦, 好吧, 我想我们正常速度 行动的话, 我...
Oh, well, I thought we were moving at kind of a normal speed. I...
好的, 我不再需要空间了 我的意思是...
Well, I don't need any more space. I mean...
你知道的, 这不是我想我们结婚 或者其他的什么, 但是我...
You know, it's not like I expect us to get married or anything, but I...
好的, 这是什么? 我的意思是, 这是...
Well, what is it? I mean, is it...?
这是我的鼻息吗? 我的意思是, 我并不需要用鼻子呼吸
Is it the way I snort? I mean, because I don't have to snort.
或者这是...?这是做爱?因为...
Or is it the...? Is it the sex? Because....
你知道的, 我能... 我能忍受
You know, I could... I could get a manual or something.
哦, 不
Well, no.
不, 你不必解释
No, you don't have to explain.
不, 不, 你知道吗? 你知道吗? 我必须...我必须走了
No. No, you know what? You know what? I have to... I have to go.
别担心晚餐, 我...
Don't worry about dinner. I....
隔壁的弗莱敏夫人 邀请我去一个意外的...
Mrs. Flammenbaum next door invited me to a surprise...
...小聚会. 你知道吗? 我必须走了
...keg party. You know what? I have to go.
好的
Okay.
再见
Bye.
联邦调查局(FBI)总部 纽约
- 这就是该死的健康计划  - 你没开玩笑吧
-This is where the health plan kicks in.  -You ain't kidding.
- 早晨好, 长官  - 嗨
-Morning, sir.  -Hey.
我想要和你聊会, 如果可以的话
I'd really like to talk to you for a minute, if I could.
哈特, 你哭了吗?
Hart, have you been crying?
不, 不, 我没哭 我甚至没有泪腺
No. No. I don't cry. I don't even have tear ducts.
萨姆福勒, 上周刚从芝加哥调来...
Sam Fuller. Transferred in from Chicago last week...
...因为控制不好情绪
...because of anger-management problems.
真的吗? 她看上去不像是那种人
Really? She seems like such a people person.
我已经想的很清楚了...
I've been giving this a lot of thought...
...也看到了很多事实 我在行动中出现了很多问题, 根据...
...and given the fact that going out on ops has become problematic in light of...
...银行事件...
...the bank thing....
好的, 我决定成为FBI的新形象代言
Well, I have decided to become the new face of the FBl.
我真的想在这儿支持总局...
I really wanna be there and support the Bureau...
...并给妇女做出一个正面的榜样 我觉得这是伟大的...
...and be a positive role model for women. I feel like this is a great ti...
哦, 是的, 你不看不到我站在这里嘛
Oh, yeah. No way you could've seen me standing there.
- 对不起  - 你说什么?
-Sorry.  -You were saying?
嗨! 唷!
Hey! Yo!
- 来个真正的"道歉", 怎样?  - 再说一次?
-How about a real "sorry," huh?  -Come again?
- 你听到我了  - 这好像要闹大了
-You heard me.  -This is gonna be great.
我说, 一个真正的"道歉"怎样?
I said, how about a real "sorry"?
如果你不退下的话 你会感到一些真正的疼痛
You are about to feel some real pain if you don't back off.
嗨, 你知道什么? 不要和我说疼痛 姐姐, 我知道疼痛
Hey, you know what? Don't talk to me about pain, sister. I invented pain.
不, 你刚刚叫我姐姐
No, you didn't just call me sister.
我没想到看见了一个小小的, 瘦屁股的,在餐桌边长大的白人女孩
I don't recall seeing a little, skinny -ass white girl at the table growing up.
嗨! 首先, 谢谢你说我瘦
Hey! First of all, thank you for calling me skinny.
第二, 你有什么问题?
Second of all, what is your problem?
然后第三, 你最好和我道歉, 否则...
And third of all, you better apologize to me or...
- 打我!  - 你知道, 我不打废物, 来吧
-Make me!  -You know, I don't make trash. Come on!
- 来吧  - 结束吧, 福勒, 去冲个澡
-Come on.  -Knock it off, Fuller. Take a shower.
那是对的, 去洗澡吧, 滚开
That's right, take a shower. Walk away.
- 你该庆幸你还能走!  - 你还想怎么样?
-You lucky you still can walk!  -You want more?
- 洗澡吧, 走吧  - 来呀
-Take a shower. Go on.  -Come here.
那是对的, 继续, 走过来
That's right, go on. Keep walking.
哈特
Hart
你刚才说什么了?
You were saying?
哦, 一个女性的正面形象, 长官
Oh, a positive role model for women, sir.
在我们确定任何出场之前 我想要你和某人谈谈
I want you to talk to someone before we schedule any appearances.
能提供个人形象建议的某人
Someone who can help with personal -presentation issues.
服装, 化妆, 等等 他是很多人推荐的
Clothing, makeup, so forth. He comes very highly recommended.
我只是在庆典的时候装扮过
I just went through a makeover for the pageant.
我现在还很反感那些头发定型剂
I'm still getting hairspray off my butt.
什么? 它能防止泳装缩水, 谢谢
What? It prevents the bathing suit from riding up. Thank you.
长官, 我不想再次成为FBI芭比
Sir, I just don't wanna become FBl Barbie again.
你的选择是什么?
What's your option?
你不能再去现场了 这会给你自己和同事带来危险的
You can't go in the field without putting yourself and agents in jeopardy.
- 你的那种生涯结束了 长官, 那不行
-That part of your life is over.  -Sir, it can't be.
我是我仅有的所知该去怎么做 那是我仅有的
That's all that I know how to do. That's all that I have.
你必须做个选择 坐在办公桌前处理文件...
You gotta make a choice. Sit at a desk pushing papers...
...或者在这里提升总局的形象?
...or be out there boosting the Bureau's image?
听着, 当你作出决定的时候 请让我知道
Look, when you make up your mind, let me know.
瑞切尔, 马休斯的调动文件过来了吗?
Rachel, did those transfer papers for Matthews come through?
在你桌上, 长官
On your desk, sir.
长官, 马休斯探员要调去哪里?
Sir, is Agent Matthews going someplace?
迈阿密
Miami.
他要成为分局指挥官的助手 这小伙子升的很高了
He's gonna be assistant SAC. Going to the top, that boy.
长官
Sir.
抱歉
Sorry.
你知道, 我要去见你让我见的那个人
You know, I'll meet whoever you want me to meet.
太好了
Good.
哦, 我希望她不是个胖子
Oh, I hope she's not a fatty.
祖尔梅尔斯, 这是格雷西 哈特
Joel Myers, Gracie Hart.
哦, 是的
Oh, yes.
是的
Yes.
我能胜任这个工作
I can work with this.
你会成为我的西斯廷教堂里的 蒙娜丽莎
You will be my Mona Lisa, my Sistine Chapel.
- 我能在原石中发现雕塑  - 慢点, 达芬奇
-I will find the sculpture in the stone.  -Slow down, da Vinci.
你觉得向上托的纹胸怎样?
How do you feel about a pushup bra?
你觉得泰瑟枪安全套怎样?
How do you feel about a genital -shocking taser gun?
我可以试试
I'm open to it.
好的
Okay.
你准备好成为FBI的新形象代言了吗?
Are you open to new experiences, like becoming the face of the FBl?
- 我参加过庆典, 我能做好  - 那只是三天, 而现在是你的生活
-I did the pageant, I can do this.  -That was three days. This is your life.
这就像是要教狗狗新技能
That was teaching a dog a few new tricks.
这是要教狗成为蝴蝶
This is teaching a dog to become a butterfly.
倒不是指你是狗 它们的毛发通常都很光滑
Not that you're a dog. They generally have smoother hair.
听着, 只是...你知道, 只要告诉我 你需要我去做什么, 然后我会去做的
Look, just... You know, just tell me what you want me to do, and I'll do it.
- 规则一, 不许冲撞  - 什么?
-Rule number one, no hitting.  -What?
FBI的形象代言用她的语言 而不是拳头或者椅子
The face of the FBl uses her words, not her fists or a chair.
规则二, 咀嚼的时候闭上嘴
Rule number two, chew with your mouth closed.
- 你不知道我是怎么吃饭的  - 你到处都有番茄酱污渍
-You don't know how I eat.  -You have ketchup stains all over you.
如果不是从嘴里掉出来的 那它们是怎么出现的?
How did they get there if they didn't fall from an open orifice?
我不知道, 也许我在番茄树下经过
I don't know. Maybe I walked under a ketchup tree.
规则三, 不要有鼻息
Rule number three, no snorting.
你为什么不拿去看看这个列表
Why don't you just take the list.
我相信你有能力成为 经典而时尚的
And I truly believe you are capable of great class and style.
然后, 我能说, 我现在也刚失恋嘛
And, may I say, I also recently went through a breakup.
我现在没有失恋
I didn't go through a breakup.
浮肿的眼睛, 没有睡觉, 易怒
Puffy eyes, no sleep, irritable.
其他探员其实也告诉我了
And some of the other agents told me about it.
但是相信我, 只要照我说的做 你会让他后悔的...
But believe me, you do as I say, and you will make him regret it...
...因为人们只会在乎 在乎他们自己的人
...because people care about people who care about themselves.
- 所以都在这里了?  - 不, 都在这里
-So it's all in here?  -No, it's all in here.
美国需要明星, 所以你要成为明星
America wants a star. So you have to become a star.
你要注意穿着, 然后对待打扮 你的朋友们就像你是个明星
You have to dress and treat your friends like you're a star.
你对待自己在必须像个明星 在你...
You have to treat yourself like a star. Before you...
我知道, 我知道, 我是大明星
I know, I know. I'm a big star!
我们的下一位嘉宾是 去年美国小姐庆典的亚军
Our next guest was the runner -up at last year's Miss United States pageant.
十个月后...
我们发现她其实是个FBI探员...
We found out she was actually an FBl agent...
...在庆典上执行一个阻止袭击的认为
...on a mission to thwart an attack on the pageant.
你能在她的新书中看到这一段故事...
You can read about it in her new book...
...从坏脾气小姐到最具亲和力小姐
...From Misdemeanors to Miss Congeniality.
这就是格雷西 哈特探员
Here's Agent Gracie Hart.
- 嗨, 格雷西  - 瑞吉斯, 很高兴见到你
-Hi, Gracie.  -Regis. Good to see you.
- 乔伊  - 过得怎么样?
-Joy.  -How are you?
- 好漂亮的衣服  - 谢谢, 你看上去很美
-What a great suit.  -Thank you, and you look fabulous.
- 谢谢  - 这不是我想像中的FBI探员
-Thank you.  -This is not how I picture an FBl agent.
你一点也不像约翰 埃德加 胡佛
You don't look anything like J. Edgar Hoover.
哦, 是吗? 因为他的服装吧
Oh, really? Because this is his dress.
- 听着, 我看了庆典...  - 我打赌你看了, 瑞吉斯
-Listen, I watched the pageant...  -I bet you did, Regis.
每年, 事实上. 那很令人为难
Every year, actually. It's embarrassing.
我最喜欢的部分是女性的自我防御 你知道吗?
My favorite part was the women's self -defense thing, you know?
你能给我们重演一下吗?
Could you give us an encore?
事实上, 我再也不做了 现在有人保护我了
Actually, I don't do that anymore. I have someone who does it for me.
所以, 如果可以的话 让我引荐我的朋友, 萨姆福勒探员
So, if I could, I'd like to bring out a little friend of mine, Agent Sam Fuller...
...让她来给我们演示一下
...who will be helping us with the demonstration.
这就是她
Here she is.
那么, 瑞吉斯, 你能去垫子那边嘛
So, Regis, if we could have you come over to the mat.
福勒
Fuller
站在这儿, 让福勒在你前面
Stand right here with Fuller in front of you.
- 好吧, 瑞吉斯, 掐住她  - 她看上去不高兴
-All right, Regis, grab her.  -She looks angry.
- 我必须掐住她吗?  - 去吧, 她没有其他位置了
-Do I have to grab her?  -Go ahead. She has no place else to be.
好的, 女士们, 如果你还记得 这个单词"SING", 腹腔神经...
All right, ladies, if you'll please remember, the word is "SlNG." Solar plexus...
...脚背...
...instep...
...鼻子...
...nose...
- ...和腹股沟  - 不要腹股沟! 不!
-...and groin.  -Not the groin! No!
很好, 谢谢, 福勒探员
Very nice. Thank you, Agent Fuller.
来吧, 瑞吉斯, 让我们扶你起来
Come on, Regis, let's get you up.
谢谢, 格雷西, 作为打了我丈夫 的一个特殊的回请...
Thanks, Gracie. And as a special treat for knocking my husband around...
...我也有个小小的惊喜给你 我知道你认识这些人
...l have a little surprise for you. I think you know these people.
这是谢丽尔弗雷泽, 美国小姐 和斯坦费尔特, 庆典的主办者
Here's Cheryl Frazier, Miss United States, and Stan Fields, host of the pageant.
是你!
It's you!
- 我喜欢你的口红  - 是吗? 丝荻拉为我挑的
-I love your lipstick.  -You do? Stila made it for me.
- 他们以我命名的, 它叫格雷西  - 那听上去真棒
-They named it after me. It's called Gracie.  -That makes sense.
- 你做了你的头发  - 这是加亮了一下
-You did something to your hair.  -Just a couple of highlights.
- 一些?  - 好的好的...
-A couple?  -Okay, okay...
...小姐, 我再也不会扎起来了 因为那会使我的脸看上去太长
...Miss I'll -Never -Grow -My -Bangs -Out - Because -It'll -Make -My -Face -Too -Long.
我想我们都应该坐在干燥器下
I feel we should all be sitting under dryers.
这就是好朋友见面的场景
That's what happens when best friends get together.
但愿我能请出我的好朋友, 罗杰科尔曼...
Wish we could have invited my best friend, Roger Coleman...
...但是上周他被卡车无意地撞了
...but he got hit by a Goodwill truck last week.
是吗?
Really?
我们现在来点广告吧? 请
Don't we have a commercial coming up? Please.
- 见到你真是太好了  - 我也是, 我...
-It's so good to see you.  -It's so good to see you. I...
- 格雷西, 我很抱歉打断一下 我们还有另外一场录音
Gracie, I'm sorry to interrupt. We have another taping.
哦, 谢里尔, 祖尔梅尔斯, 我的造型师
Oh, Cheryl, Joel Myers, my stylist.
美国小姐, 真高兴见到你 这是我的发型助理, 珍妮
Miss United States, such a joy to meet you. This is my hair assistant, Janine.
- 很荣幸  - 化妆和低音吉他手, 帕姆
-A pleasure.  -And on makeup and bass guitar, Pam.
- 阁下, 很荣幸 你好像把王冠戴错了
-Your Majesty.  -And you're having a bad crown day.
抱歉, 这是私人谈话时间
Excuse me, private conversation in progress.
- 滴答  - 好的
-Ticktock.  -Okay.
我很抱歉最近没打电话
I'm sorry I haven't called in a while.
不用道歉, 等我届满了 我们有很多时间聊天
Don't apologize. We'll have plenty of time to talk once I'm de -queened.
- 哦, 那听上去很痛苦  - 是的, 我真想你
-Oh, that sounds painful.  -Oh, I really miss you.
- 和艾瑞克...  - 哦, 好的...
-And Eric.  -Oh, well...
...事实上艾瑞克和我不再是以前的艾瑞克和我了
...actually Eric and I aren't Eric and I anymore.
- 什么? 什么时候的事?  - 哦, 10个月了吧
-What? Since when?  -Oh, just 1 0 months.
- 10个月?  - 是的, 我不想打扰你
-Ten months?  -Yeah, I didn't wanna bother you.
你很忙, 我很忙, 我不想打电话 来说"我们分手了", 这不是大事
You're busy, I'm busy. I didn't wanna call and say, "We broke up." It's no big deal.
哈特小姐? 我的女儿想要你的亲笔签名
Miss Hart? My daughter would love your John Hancock.
- 她叫什么名字?  - 劳伦
-What's her name?  -Lauren.
劳伦
Lauren.
那么, 发生了什么?
So, what happened?
哦, 我不得不结束 因为他变得, 你知道的, 太黏乎了
Oh, I just had to end it because he was getting, you know, really clingy.
是的, 但是我很好, 没事, 一切都好
Yeah, but I'm fine. I'm good. I'm great.
我们需要在5点赶到一个 摔跤比赛的现场直播...
We need to get to Live at 5 for a wrestling demonstration...
...然后晚上在你的出版商那里 还有一个鸡尾酒会
...then there's a cocktail party at your publisher's apartment.
我能去做下日光浴吗
I could go for a little tanning time.
你可以去两妙种 这两秒钟你是自由的
You're gonna go for a little unemployment time in about two seconds.
你可以好心替我去趟星巴克吗?
Could you be a sweetheart and get me a Starbucks?
我非常想要一杯冰的 焦糖玛奇雅朵咖啡
I am dying for an iced Venti Caramel Macchiato.
给你自己也再买些好了
Get yourself a little something too.
让我来告诉你我什么时候 可以给你买冰的焦糖玛奇雅朵咖啡
Let me tell you when I'm gonna get you an iced Venti Caramel Macchiato.
当他们在美国独立战争的时候 选个黑人妇女作总统
When they elect a black woman president of the Daughters of the American Revolution.
好的, 如果可能的话 我还想要些松饼
Okay. And if that happens, I'd also like one of those little muffins.
你喜欢它哪里?
Where would you like it?
福勒, 我能感觉到你对我有些敌意 我想我们需要谈一下
Fuller, I'm sensing a little subtle hostility, and I think we should talk about it.
福勒, 你不应该把事情都闷在心里
Fuller, you shouldn't keep things bottled up.
- 福勒, 你有什么问题吗?  - 我的问题是, 我不喜欢你
-Fuller! What is your problem?  -The problem is, I don't like you.
为什么你不放弃呢, 我让你有 这份工作...
Why don't you quit. I let you have this job...
是为了卖麦克唐纳一个人情...
as a favor to McDonald...
... 因为没人愿意和你一起工作...
...because no one outside of the canine unit would work with you...
- ...由于你的态度问题  - 你知道为什么吗? 因为我不属于这里
-...because of your little attitude problem.  -You know what? I'm out of here.
等等, 你还去星巴克吗?
Wait. Are you still going to Starbucks?
斯隆山谷 内华达州
滚!
Go!
没人能打败我的小兄弟! 我们走, 走, 付钱
No one beats my little bro! Let's go, let's go, pay up.
来吧, 付钱, 来吧, 谁是下一个?
Come on, pay up. Come on, who's next?
让我们把赌注放在桌上, 因为...
Let's get the bets on the table because...
- 是的  - 他在那里吗?
-Yeah?  -Is he there?
- 是的, 他在这里  - 好的, 是他拿了我的钱吗?
-Yeah, he's here.  -Well, has he got my money?
等等, 我来问问
Hold on, I'll ask.
抱歉, 汉兰特, 你欠格兰特先生 500美元. 你拿走了吗?
Excuse me, Highlander, you owe Mr. Grant 500 bucks. You got it?
消失
Get lost.
他说他没, 格兰特先生
He says he doesn't have it, Mr. Grant.
好的! 好的!
Okay! Okay!
他看上去找到了钱, 格兰特先生
He seems to have discovered some cash, Mr. Grant.
好的, 我会给你的男孩们 再另外找个人的
Good. All right, I got another one for you boys.
谁是记号?
Who's the mark?
这会是你本子上的一个
This is gonna be one for your scrapbook.
- 非常感谢, 请问你的名字?  - 奥克塔薇尔
-Thank you very much. Your name, please?  -Octavia.
我想你是否能告诉我 你是用什么护肤方法的?
I was wondering if you could tell me what skin -care regimen you use.
好的, 我很尽可能多地挤掉脓疮
Well, I like to catch as many felons as possible.
这使我心跳有力,加速的循环 使得我的面色得到改善
It really gets the heart pumping, and the increased circulation helps my complexion.
- 走好, 非常感谢  - 谢谢
-There you go. Thank you very much.  -Thank you.
- 嗨  - 嗨, 请问你的名字?
-Hey.  -Hey. Your name, please?
- 普丽西拉  -普丽西拉
-Priscilla.  -Priscilla.
我要做一个读书报告
I have to do a book report.
然后我想写关于你的书 因为我也想做一个探员
And I wanna do it on your book because I wanna be an agent too.
哦, 好的, 这很好, 谢谢, 普丽西拉
Oh, well, good for you. Thank you, Priscilla.
- 嗨, 你的名字?  - 安吉拉
-Hi. Your name is?  -Angela.
其他孩子的读书报告都是写 碧昂丝或者布兰妮...
The other kids are doing their report on Beyonce or Britney...
...但是如果你来我们学校演讲
...but if you come to my school and talk...
...他们就能见识到为什么做探员会这么酷...
...they'd see why being an agent is so cool...
- ...然后开始停止嘲笑我  - 我非常愿意去...
-...and stop getting on me.  -I would really love to...
...但是就像你看见的这样, 我现在很忙
...but as you can see, the agency's got me pretty busy.
走好, 谢谢
There you go. Thank you.
你能做的就是偶尔把头发梳起来 这会使你的脸露在外面...
What you could do is pull your hair up once in a while. It would open up your face...
...因为记住, 人们只在乎 在乎自己的人
...because remember, people care about people who care about themselves.
- 好的  - 嗨, 你的名字
-Okay.  -Hi. Your name is?
- 杰森  -杰森
- Jason  - Jason
如果你改变了主意记住是P.S.31 普丽西拉, 卡丹小姐的班级
If you change your mind, it's P.S. 31 , Priscilla, Miss Gordan's class.
记住了, 非常感谢 请问你的名字?
Got it. Thank you very much. Your name, please?
- 詹姆斯  - 等等!
-James.  -Wait!
你还没写下来!
You're not writing it down!
总局的训练, 我能记住很多繁杂的信息
Bureau training. I can retain enormous amounts of information.
P.S.31, 普丽西拉, 卡丹小姐的班级, 是吗?
P.S. 31 , Priscilla, Miss Gordan's class. See?
不要忘记头发的建议 可以试试卷发
And don't forget the hair tip. Try some bows.
- 走好, 谢谢  - 很高兴见到你
-There you go. Thank you.  -Nice to meet you.
很抱歉听到美国小姐的事情
And sorry to hear what happened to Miss United States.
发生什么了阿?
What happened?
谢丽尔弗雷泽最后一次被看见 是在拉斯维加斯的老年人之家...
Cheryl Frazier was last seen outside this Las Vegas senior -citizen home...
...和庆典主办者斯坦费尔特一起
...accompanied by longtime pageant host, Stan Fields.
在这次慈善活动后 他们俩乘上了豪华轿车...
The two were walking to a limo after a goodwill mission...
...去拜访当地居民
...visiting the residents here.
显然, 美国小姐和司仪费尔特 被强迫进了一辆卡车...
Apparently, Miss United States and emcee Fields were forced into a truck....
他们受伤了吗? 他们还活着吗? 这到底发生了什么?
Are they hurt? Are they alive? What demands have been made?
这是我们知道的全部, 当你去 维加斯的时候我们将会知道更多
That's all we know. You'll find out more when you get to Vegas.
指挥官想让你就这将事面对公众
The director wants you to handle publicity on this.
如果公众们看见你上电视 他们就会放心
Public sees you on TV, they'll feel reassured.
显然地, 我到底能帮上什么
Absolutely, whatever I can do to help.
立刻把你自己打扮好 飞机8点起飞
Get your beauty team assembled immediately. The jet leaves at 0800.
你要带上保镖去 他们在维加斯被绑架了
I want you to have a bodyguard out of New York. They're strapped in Vegas.
- 长官, 为什么我需要保镖?  - 人群太多太杂了
-Sir, why do I need a bodyguard?  -Crowd control.
你会成为维加斯最热的名人的
You're gonna be the hottest celebrity in Vegas.
- 如果韦恩纽顿不在的话  - 哦, 那当然, 长官, "谢谢"
-Assuming Wayne Newton isn't in town.  -Oh, of course, sir. "Danke Schoen."
福勒! 我需要你陪哈特 一起坐飞机去维加斯
Fuller! I want you on a plane to Vegas with Hart.
你要就谢丽尔弗雷泽绑架事件 去做公众处理
She's gonna do publicity on the Cheryl Frazier kidnapping.
不去
Not going.
- 你刚才是在拒绝命令吗?  - 我不能忍受她, 长官
-Did you just refuse an order?  -I can't take her, sir.
我会杀了她的, 我很乐意
I'll kill her. And I'll enjoy it.
福勒, 你离撤职很近
Fuller, you are this close to being gone.
没人愿意和你一起工作 无论是芝加哥还是这儿
Nobody wants to work with you in Chicago or here.
那对我很好, 我喜欢独自工作
That's fine by me. I like to work alone.
然后成为灯塔看守人 这是FBI, 我们讲究团队合作
Then become a lighthouse keeper. This is the FBl. We like partners.
她就像是屁股里的刺 她很自以为是而且...
She's a pain in the ass. She's conceited and...
让人们远离她, 保证她安全 你是去做保镖, 我会给你找个拍档的
Keep people off her. Keep her safe. You be a good bodyguard, I'll find you a partner.
如果这次你干砸了, 你就滚蛋吧
You blow this, you're gone. Period.
顺便说一句 在瑞吉斯的节目上你们俩我都爱
And by the way, I loved you both on Regis.
- 格兰特  - 男孩们
-Grant.  -Boys.
格兰特先生
Mr. Grant.
我们看看你给我带来了什么
Let's see what you got for me.
- 斯坦费尔特和...  - 美国小姐
-Stan Fields and...  -Miss United States.
你知道庆典委员会会付多少来 赎回她吗? 好几百万
You know what the pageant will pay to get her back? Millions.
- 所以你是说我们为了敲诈而抓她的  - 不
-So you're saying we hold her for ransom?  -No.
我抓她是为了敲诈 而你则是为了尝新鲜
I hold her for ransom, and you get a taste.
把她带上我的车
Bring her to my car.
我有点饿了
I'm a little bit hungry.
嗨! 是我们绑架了她
Hey! We grabbed her.
白痴, 你干不了这活 联邦调查局的人马上就会找到你的
Moron, you can't handle this job. The feds will come right down on you.
别叫我白痴, 我在美术方面 获得了学士学位, 而我的兄弟...
Don't call me a moron. I got a BA in Fine Arts, and my brother....
- 不要叫我白痴  - 当我找到你的时候, 你是失业的
-Don't call me a moron.  -You were unemployed when I found you.
你都保不住在脱衣舞表演的工作
You couldn't keep a job on the show in the Strip.
是我办的表演! 那是我的主意
I made that show! It was my concept.
然后突然他们改变主意了 告诉我和路易我们不符合他们的标准了
Then suddenly they change it and tell me and Lou we're not up to their standards.
现在你为我工作
You work for me now.
- 路易  - 我在这
-Lou.  -I'm there.
那我拉回去!
Bring me back up!
她是你们的了! 她是你们的了! 让我上来! 让我上来!
She's yours! She's all yours! Let me up! Let me up.
让我上来, 哦, 上帝, 让我上来
Just let me up. Oh, God, let me up.
下次, 他就放手了
Next time, he lets go.
你们这群疯子!
You guys are crazy!
现在怎么办?
Now what?
现在按他说的办 我们绑架了她
Now we do exactly what he said. We ransom her.
请小心点, 我的枪在这包里
Please be careful. My guns are in that Fendi.
谢谢, 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
请告诉我你有去太阳马戏团的票
Please tell me you have tickets to see Cirque du Soleil.
- 我是你的保镖  - 什么?
-I'm your bodyguard.  -What?
麦克唐纳认为我俩很合适 由于我们在瑞吉斯节目上表现...
McDonald thinks we have a bond because of our performance on Regis...
...还有TRL, 奥普拉和食品网络
...and TRL, Oprah, the Food Network.
哦, 嗨, 嗨, 我们开始协调了从那以后 柠檬鸡? 重味的
Oh, hey, hey, we got some great recipes from that one. The lemon chicken? Tangy.
现在, 听着, 像所有的伟大团队一样
Now, look, like all great teams,
霍普和克罗斯比，弗雷德和金杰...
Hope and Crosby, Fred and Ginger...
...奥特卡斯特...
....Outkast...
...总会有结束的时候...
...the end must come...
...所以, 再见
...so bye -bye.
让我简单点告诉你, 哈特 麦克唐纳给了我一个任务...
Let me make this simple for you, Hart. McDonald gave me a mission...
...而这个计划不会被取消 除非我们都不在了, 懂了吗?
...so that plane does not take off unless we're both on it. Got it?
你可以不要那么认真
You might consider a Tic Tac.
请...
Please...
...我们现在在设法合作
...we're trying to cooperate.
- 闭上你的嘴  - 你不能对她那么说话
-Shut your mouth.  -You can't talk to her like that.
- 你想要告诉我该怎么做吗?  - 不, 我只是一个司仪
-You trying to tell me what to do?  -No, I'm just the emcee.
我听过你唱歌, 真幸运我现在不开枪打你
I've heard you sing. Lucky I don't shoot you now.
好的, 把那举起来
Okay, let's line this up.
- 然后...  - 我戴我的王冠
-And....  -I don't have my crown.
- 谁会在意呢?  - 我在意
-Who cares?  -I care.
- 很好  - 成千上万的...
-Fine.  -Thousands of women...
- ...美国的女性在乎  - 给她她的王冠
-...all across America care.  -Give her the crown.
在公众面前, 美国小姐总是很自豪地 戴着她的王冠
When in public, Miss United States always proudly wears her crown.
好了吧?
Okay?
好的, 让我们再来一次
All right, let's go again.
一, 二, 开始
One, two, action.
我们被绑架了, 这里有两个人...
We've been kidnapped, and there's two men here...
...他们说要在周五的 午夜时分杀了我们
...who say they're gonna kill us by Friday at midnight.
但是我不想要任何人付给他们钱
But I don't want anyone to pay them any money.
- 咔  - 不要向恐怖主义屈服
-Cut!  -That would be giving in to terrorism...
...我是美国小姐...
...and I'm Miss United States...
- 咔  - ...我代表公平和正义...
-Cut!  -...and I stand for fairness and decency...
...还有美国!
...and the American way!
我说, 咔!
I said, cut!
如果你愿意我很高兴我来说
I'd be happy to say it if you'd like.
我在剧院里经常说
I've done quite a bit of theater.
我在"十二夜"里扮演过拉戈
I played lago in Twelfth Night.
联邦调查局(FBI)总部 拉斯维加斯
再派两架直升机
Put two more choppers up.
- 长官
Sir.
- 格雷西 哈特  - 是的
-Gracie Hart.  -Yes.
- 我是沃尔特 科林斯  - 长官
-I'm Walter Collins.  -Sir.
我觉得我像是站在女王面前
I feel as though I'm in the presence of royalty.
哦, 不, 长官, 我不是女王 我只是亚军
Oh, no, sir, I'm not queen, just runner -up.
我很高兴引荐给你, 萨姆福勒探员
I would like to present to you Agent Sam Fuller.
- 福勒  - 长官
-Fuller.  -Sir.
- 祖尔梅尔斯 珍妮和帕姆  - 梅尔斯 珍妮 帕姆
-Joel Myers, Janine and Pam.  -Joel, Janine, Pam.
你们为什么不先去宾馆 当我在给探员们做报告的时候
Why don't we get you to the hotel while I give the agents a debriefing.
哦, 那太糟了, 距离上次我听到的 精彩报告已经过去几个月了
Oh, that's too bad. It's been months since I've had a good debriefing.
虽然, 我当时只是拳击短裤
Although, I'm really more of a boxers man.
好的, 错误的听众
Okay, wrong audience.
哈特探员, 福勒探员, 这是 富尔曼探员, 你们的联系人
Agent Hart, Agent Fuller, this is Agent Foreman. He's your liaison.
- 如果你需要什么, 杰夫是你的随从  - 好的
-You need anything, Jeff is your boy.  -Good.
欢迎来到拉斯维加斯
Welcome to Las Vegas
当我的女朋友发现我要和你一起 工作的时候, 她快要死了
When my girlfriend found out that I would be working with you, she almost died.
是的, 她也是个探员
Yeah, she's an agent too.
她认为我会爱上你
She actually thought that I was gonna fall for you.
我告诉她...我说, "珍妮特, 这不可能"
I told her... I said, "Janet, there's no way..."
富尔曼, 我们不要说这些了
Foreman, we talked about this.
对不起, 长官, 总之, 你对我来说 太老了, 所以...
Sorry, sir. Anyway, you're obviously too old for me, so....
哦, 好的, 那真是卸下了一个大负担
Oh, good, well, that's a load off.
弗雷泽和菲尔兹在老年中心 的节目中的出场...
Frazier and Fields make an appearance at a senior center for a program...
...在那里老人们花时间和孩子们在一起 菲尔兹先生的母亲就在那里
...where the elderly spend time with kids. Mr. Fields' mother is there.
我知道你们在这干的...
I think what you're doing here...
...显示出不同代人 有很多东西需要互相学习
...shows that different generations have so much to learn from each other.
我说, 我就从我的祖母那里 学到了很多...
I mean, I know I learned a lot from my grandmother...
...特别是, 怎样杀鸡
...specifically, how to kill a chicken.
虽然我不喜欢那样做...
And even though it wasn't something I enjoyed doing...
...我永远不会忘记它们临死前的叫声
...I'll never forget the sound of their death squawks.
但是如果我不得不杀鸡 我就知道该怎么做了
But if I had to kill a chicken, I'd know how.
他们结束以后
They finish their appearance.
直奔豪华轿车 就在那他们被袭击和绑架了
Head for the limo, where they're attacked and kidnapped.
我们从监视探头里 得到了这段录像
We got this video from a surveillance camera.
我们所能看到的就是两个蒙面人 一辆卡车和一个假牌照
All we have is two hooded figures, the make of the truck and a fake license plate.
我们和豪华轿车死机谈话, 但是他说 他什么也没看到, 就是这样
We talked to the limo driver, but he says he didn't see anything. And that's it.
这是你们的简报文件夹
These are your briefing folders.
嗨, 明天早上9点, 在你的宾馆里 你还有个记者招待会
Hart, you have a press conference at your hotel at 0900 tomorrow morning.
- 如果有什么问题, 打电话给你  - 长官?
-Call me if there's any questions.  -Sir?
- 我们必须找到她  - 我会找到她
-We have to find her.  -I'll find her.
我知道我们的行程很紧...
I know we're on a tight schedule...
...但是如果你们想看什么表演 告诉我, 珍妮特能为我们搞到票
...but if you guys wanna see any shows, just let me know. Janet can get us tickets.
我不知道她是怎么做的, 但是她确实能办到
I don't know how she does it, but she does it.
她真的很厉害 是神射手, 还会烹饪
She's really great. Expert marksman. She bakes.
哦, 我差点忘了 这是你们的电子身份卡
Oh, almost forgot. Here are your coded ID cards.
你们需要这个才能进出局里 这是你的耳机
You're gonna need these to get into the Bureau. And here are your earpieces.
我们...谢谢
We're... Thanks.
我们的频率是1145
We're gonna be on frequency 1 1 45.
抱歉, 这不是FBI的装备
Sorry, that is not FBl issue.
这是我为珍妮特买的毛衣 为了庆祝她的生日
That's a sweater that I bought for Janet for her birthday.
这是配套的帽子 菱形格子的, 她是苏格兰人
And that's the hat that goes with it. Argyle. She's Scottish.
珍妮特麦卡伦
Janet McCarren.
我很抱歉, 我正陷于爱河之中
Look, I'm sorry. I'm just really in love.
有什么好地方让我呕吐一下吗?
Where's the best place for me to throw up?
我很为你高兴, 杰夫
Well, I am thrilled for you, Jeff.
因为, 不像福勒探员 我, 也是碳元素构成的
Because, unlike Agent Fuller, I, too, am carbon -based.
威尼斯宾馆
The Venetian Hotel.
哈特小姐
Miss Hart!
真是太荣幸了, 我是罗伯托 费尼斯威尼斯宾馆的经理
What a fantastic pleasure. I am Roberto Fenice, manager of the Venetian Hotel.
- 哦, 你好  - 你的愿望就是我的命令
-Oh, hello.  -Your wish is my command.
哦, 我希望你不要亲吻我的手表 那不是防水的
Oh, well, I wish you wouldn't kiss my watch. It's not water -resistant.
这行动要比我这几个月做的多很多 所以我们走吧
Although it's more action than I've had in months, so go ahead.
- 哈特小姐, 你很甜美  - 费尼斯先生
-Miss Hart, you are delicious.  -Mr. Fenice.
嗨, 我是富尔曼探员 这是萨姆福勒探员
Hi, I'm Agent Foreman. This is Agent Sam Fuller.
- 哦, 我的天! 这是格雷西 哈特!  - 你没开玩笑吧!
-Oh, my gosh! It's Gracie Hart!  -You're kidding!
- 哪里?  - 就在那!
-Where?  -Right there!
格雷西!
Gracie!
格雷西! 嗨! Grac...
Gracie! Hey! Grac...
福勒!
Fuller!
- 哦, 我的天!  - 福勒!
-Oh, my!  -Fuller!
好了, 退下! 退下!
All right, down! Down!
够了, 够了, 够了, 福勒, 福勒
Too much, too much, too much. Fuller, Fuller.
福勒, 我认为你没理解"太多"的含义!
Fuller, I don't think you fully understand the concept of "too much" !
嗨, 麦克唐纳告诉我要 不要让人们保接近你的
Hey, McDonald told me to keep people off you.
而且我没想到老爷爷会跟在后面 至少不在他能力范围
And I don't think grandpa's coming back. At least, not under his own power.
也许我们应该在财富岛的, 嗯哼?
Maybe we should've stayed at Treasure Island, huh?
- 你穿运动衫不好看  - 那是最好的了
-You don't see that in Jersey.  -It's the best.
一艘轮船沉了, 这里现在到处都是 缺少衣服的海员
A ships sinks, and there's all these scantily clad sailors around.
- 使得我也想去加入海军了  - 是的, 你就是他们想要的
-Makes me wanna join the Navy.  -Yeah, you are just what they're looking for.
嗨, 哈特, 你确定这个套房够大吗?
Hey, Hart, you sure this suite is big enough for you?
我都把我的整个房间 安置在你的蒸汽浴室里
I can fit my entire room inside your steam shower.
祝你在那生活愉快
Feel free to move in there.
是的, 对的, 让我们 复习一下明天的行程表
Yeah, right. Right, let's go over this schedule for tomorrow.
- 格雷西?  - 是的
-Gracie?  -Yes.
格雷西, 电视上有谢丽尔的消息
Gracie, there's something about Cheryl on the TV.
我们刚刚收到一盒勒索录像带...
We just received what appears to be a ransom video...
...它是几小时前匿名 电邮到我们演播厅的
...which was e -mailed to our studios a few hours ago from an anonymous source.
是从一个未知的地址寄出的
It was sent from an unknown location.
我们被绑架了, 这里有两个人...
We've been kidnapped. And there's two men here...
...他们说要在周五的 午夜时分杀了我们...
...who say they're going to kill us by Friday at midnight...
...除非庆典主办方给他们500万美元
...unless they're paid $5 million by the pageant.
重复一下, 500万美元, 周五午夜
Once again, that's $5 million by Friday at midnight.
我不能只坐在这里, 我要做点什么 我应该去看看...
I can't just sit here. I have to do something. I should just see...
我应该作就你来应该做的事, 哈特
You should do exactly what you came here to do, Hart.
9点在记者招待会
Press conference at 9.
豪华轿车
Limos.
豪华轿车, 豪华轿车, 豪华轿车
Limos, limos, limos.
- 你的电话, 长官, 二线  - 谢谢
-Call for you, sir. Line two.  -Thank you.
- 科林斯  - 是的, 长官, 嗨, 我是格雷西 哈特
-Collins.  -Yes, sir, hi, this is Gracie Hart.
我在看照片, 我注意到豪华轿车...
I was looking at the visuals, and I noticed that the limousine...
- 我们和司机谈过了  - 我知道了, 但是
-We talked to the limo driver.  -I realize that, but...
- 我们从空中得到了点线索  - 别担心
-We've got something on aerial.  -Don't worry about it.
休息一会, 祝明天记者招待会顺利
Get some rest. Have a nice press conference.
好的
Okay.
谢谢, 珍妮特
Thank you, Janet.
是的, 嗨, 这是荒漠 豪华轿车服务中心吗?
Yeah, hi, is this Desert Limo Service?
是的, 我想要查找你们的一个司机
Yeah, I'm trying to locate one of your drivers.
汤姆阿伯纳西先生
A Mr. Tom Abernathy.
嗨, 格雷西 哈特在吗? FBI指挥官 威尔逊在线
Hi, is Gracie Hart there, please? I have FBl Director Wilson on the line.
我们需要和她尽快通话, 请
We need to speak with her ASAP, please.
格雷西 哈特在吗? 格雷西 哈特?
Is Gracie Hart here? Gracie Hart?
- 有人要格雷西 哈特听电话?  - 是的, 女士
-Is somebody calling for Gracie Hart?  -Yes, ma'am.
我是格雷西 哈特
I'm Gracie Hart.
- 我认识她! 格雷西 哈特在这儿!  - 是吗?
-I recognize her! Gracie Hart's here!  -Yes?
这是FBI指挥官威尔逊, 尽快, 尽快
It's FBl Director Wilson, ASAP. ASAP.
威尔逊指挥官, 谢谢, 我是哈特
Director Wilson. Thank you. Hart here.
是的, 长官, 是的, 长官
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
是的, 长官, 我准备好了
Yes, sir. I'm on it.
非常感谢, 好的, 长官, 再见
Thank you very much. Okay, sir, bye -bye.
- 你能在这里签名吗?  - 哦, 当然, 我...
-Would you please sign this?  -Oh, sure, I...
我妈妈爱你
My mom loves you.
- 而他是不轻易爱谁的  - 我也爱你, 格雷西
-And she does not love easily.  -I love you too, Gracie.
- 你很棒  - 你是如此伟大...
-You're fabulous.  -You've got such great...
谢谢, 伙计们, 谢谢你们的支持
Thank you, guys, so much for your support.
我在和和这位先生要谈一下 关于美国小姐被绑架的事情
I'm here on business to talk to this man about the Miss United States kidnapping.
- 阿伯纳西先生?  - 什么事?
-Mr. Abernathy?  -Yeah?
你在干什么?
What did you do?
她驾驶了谢丽尔弗雷泽和斯坦费尔特 乘坐的豪华轿车...
He was driving the limousine that Cheryl Frazier and Stan Fields were in...
...就在那天他们被绑架了
...the day they were kidnapped.
我想要知道为什么你停靠的 离老人之家的门口那么远?
I wanted to know why you parked so far away from the entrance of the home.
是的, 你为什么这样做? 为什么?
Yeah, why would you do that? Why?
所以, 如果我出示某物...
So if I could show you something....
好的, 不是这些, 不是我的徽章 好吧, 你为什么...?
Well, it's not these. It's not my badge. Well, what do you...?
这是我的部署计划...
It's my deployment schedule...
...如果你能看见哪里写着"明日事件"
...and if you can look where it says "tomorrow's events."
- 是的, 朗读一下, 大声一点  - "早上九点记者招待会...
-Yeah, go ahead, read aloud.  -"Nine a.m. press conference...
- ...在威尼斯酒店"?  - 大声读, 我们听不见!
-...at the Venetian"?  -Speak up, we cannot hear you!
他说"早上九点 记者招待会在威尼斯酒店"...
He said, "9 a.m. press conference at the Venetian" ...
...那儿我将面对二频道, 四频道...
...where I will be in front of channels two, four...
我的意思是, 好的, 每个人都被邀请了
I mean, well, everybody's invited.
我将有可能不得不说 汤姆阿伯纳西有嫌疑
And I will probably have to say that Tom Abernathy is a suspect.
你为什么这么说我?
Why are you doing this to me?
因为我想找到我的朋友
Because I wanna find my friends.
而且因为你可能在 这三种压力下汗流浃背...
And because you are sweating in all three stress spots...
...人们通常会在被公开羞辱前 汗流浃背的
...that people routinely start sweating in before they undergo public humiliation.
我对这很在行
I had it on Letterman.
好了, 各位, 我想要待在这儿聊聊...
Okay, everybody, I would love to stay and chat...
...但是我必须回去 挑选记者招待会的服装了
...but I have to go pick out my outfit for the press conference.
- 哦, 再说一遍, 几点?  - 九点!
-Oh, what time was that again?  -Nine!
谢谢, 看新闻 我将会大声说得
Thank you. Watch the news, I'll do a little shout out.
谢谢, 格雷西
Thanks, Gracie.
嗨! 嗨! 停下! 停下, 等等
Hey! Hey! Hold up! Hold up. Wait.
好的,  有人在那天的 前一天来找过我
Okay. Somebody came up to me the day before.
她给了我200美元如果我能 把车停在老人之家门口的远处...
She offers me 200 bucks if I will park far away from the entrance at the home...
- ...这就是全部了, 我发誓  - 她? 她什么样?
-...and that's it. That's all I know, I swear.  -She? What did she look like?
- 哦, 哈特小姐, 你介意吗?  - 哦, 我真的很赶时间
-Oh, Miss Hart, would you mind?  -Oh, I'm actually in a hurry.
- 你要见威廉王子, 那是真的吗?  - 哦, 我...
-Is it true you're seeing Prince William?  -Oh, I'm...
不, 我们只是在一个书会上谈过几句 他爱上我了, 但是我讨厌城堡
No, we were just talking at a book party. He's in love with me, but I hate castles.
- 抱歉, 抱歉, 抱歉, 嗨  - 让我来解释给你听
-Sorry, sorry, sorry. Hey.  -Let me explain something to you.
你并没有按照计划去做 而我是个计划主义者
You didn't do what was on the schedule, and I'm a schedule -type person.
你错过了记者招待会
You missed the press conference.
我去了趟局里因为我从 豪华轿车司机那里得到了一个线索...
I went to the Bureau because I got a tip from the limo driver...
...他说一个像多莉帕顿的人...
...who said that somebody who looked like Dolly Parton...
...付他钱如果他不把车 停在老年之家的门口
...paid him not to park in front of the senior home.
- 你听到了你刚才在说什么吗?  - 是的
-Did you hear what you just said?  -Yeah.
为什么你出去不向我汇报?
And why did you go out without clearing it with me?
向你汇报?
Clearing it with you?
嗨, 我想大家还没吃早饭...
Hey, I'll bet no one's had breakfast...
我很抱歉, 但是我不是为你工作的 好吗? 你为我工作, 所以...
I'm sorry, but I don't work for you. Okay? You work for me, so...
- 不, 你不能说我为你工作  - 你为我工作
-No, you didn't just say I work for you.  -You work for me.
- 你为我工作  - 闭嘴
-You work for me.  -Shut up.
福勒, 我没时间和你玩这个, 好吗?
Fuller, I don't have the time for this, okay?
听着, 我们为什么不去做点...
Listen, why don't we just get something...
好的, 看着, 我是FBI的形象代言
Okay, look. I am the face of the Bureau.
你来这儿是为了帮助我成为形象代言的 这意味着你为我工作
You are here to help me be the face of the Bureau, which means that you work for me.
这么什么大不了...
It's no big...
听着, 哈特, 我是个保镖 这就意味着我要有个人来被我保护
Look, Hart, I am your bodyguard. That means I need a body to guard!
你撞我, 这就意味着我能让你走
You hit me, which means I could bring you up on charges.
如果我能的话 我自己早就走了
If I could just bring myself up right now.
好的, 听着, 我不为你工作 你也不为我工作
Okay, look, I don't work for you. You don't work for me.
我们是一个团队, 懂了吗?
We're a team. Get it?
就像是在"如果你不听我的话, 我就可以踢你的屁股"的团队
"I will kick your sorry ass if you don't listen to me" team.
如果你还记忆清晰的话, 应该是"小屁股"
If you remember correctly, it was "skinny ass."
然后, 第二, 你的问题是什么, 福勒?
And, second of all, what is your problem, Fuller?
你的内心这的觉得舒服吗? 不断地惹恼周围的人和殴打他们的脸?
Do you honestly feel it's okay to go around harassing people and bashing their faces in?
猜猜是什么, 你在局里的情况 永远也不可能好转...
Guess what. You will never make it in this Bureau...
...如果你不用用你的脑子 你只是用...
...if you don't start using your head. You just use...
什么, 你现在开始听我说了吧?
What, you start listening to me now?
住手! 住手! 住手!
Stop it! Stop! Stop!
好吧
All right.
福勒, 暴力不能解决我们的问题 是吗? 它不能
Fuller, violence is not the answer to our problems, all right? It's not.
我不是说这是因为我"怕"你 好吗?
And I'm not just saying that because I'm "scared" of you. Okay?
因为我...那是什么?!
Because I'm... What is that?!
我呼叫麦克唐纳, 祖尔在哪? 我不嫩这样去见公众
I am calling McDonald. Where's Joel? I can't go into public like this.
嗨, 怎么样? 祖尔!
Hey, how are you? Joel!
- 你好  - 你把我的妆踢坏了
-Hello.  -You knocked my highlights off.
- 发生什么了?  - 看!
-What happened?  -Look!
- 这将要花一个小时  - 告诉关于这个
-This will take an hour.  -Tell me about it.
- 喷雾  - 女士们
-Misting.  -Ladies.
我希望我们通知一下网络 然后组织另一场记者招待会
I really think we should call the networks and set up another press conference.
你知道吗? 你很正确, 好的
You know what? You're absolutely right. Okay.
我想要去趟房间 我需要一些小小的梳理和打扮...
I'm gonna go back up to the room. I'm gonna get a little spritz, a little refresh...
是她, 是她, 拿着
It's her. It's her. Hold this.
- 我们不是在质问多莉   - 这不是真的多莉 , 所以放轻松
-We are not questioning Dolly.  -It's not the real Dolly, so relax.
我知道这不是, 离她远远的
I know it's not. Stay away from her.
好的, 我是成年人了, 如果我愿意我能做好的
Okay, I'm an adult. I can act as I please.
- 你让多莉 一个人待着  - 不许碰我
-You leave Dolly alone!  -Get your hands off me!
非常感谢, 抱歉, 冒牌多莉 !
Thank you very much. Excuse me, fake Dolly!
嗨, 你好, FBI
Hi. Hello. FBl here.
是的, 如果可以的话 我只是想和你聊几句
Yeah, I just would love to have a few words with you if I could.
- 嗨, 你好吗?  - 你是怎么做的?
-Hi, how are you?  -How you doing?
是的, 谢谢你的支持 是的, 放开我, 你这八爪鱼! 放开我!
Yeah, thank you for your support. Yeah. Get off me, you stalker! Get off me!
冒牌多莉 !
Fake Dolly!
你去哪里?
Where are you going?
哈特!
Hart!
- 冒牌多莉 !  - 格雷西!
-Fake Dolly!  -Gracie!
- 站住!  - 哈特, 站住!
-Stop!  -Hart, stop!
多莉帕顿!
Dolly Parton!
这身装饰怎么这么不合作?
What is it about this outfit that is making everyone so uncooperative?
格雷西 哈特!
Gracie Hart!
金发美女! 别拍照! 站住
Blondie! No pictures. Hold on.
抱歉, 我需要你们...
Excuse me. I need for you to...
- 让开! 只要...  - 看这!
-Open! Just...  -Watch it!
- 大家帮忙拦住那个冒牌多莉 !  - 哈特, 站住!
-Someone stop that fake Dolly!  -Hart, stop!
拦住她!
Stop her!
抱歉, 抱歉
Excuse me. Excuse me.
请不要让我做这些事 这不像是淑女干得
Please don't make me do something that's not ladylike.
好的, FBI, 我有些问题要问你
Okay, FBl. I have just a few questions for you.
我先! 你是怎么了?
Me first! What is the matter with you?
哈特小姐! 你在干什么?
Miss Hart! What are you doing?
帕顿小姐来这里是出席记者招待会 来宣布她的新的环球巡演
Miss Parton is here for a press conference to announce her new world tour.
这里没有环球巡演 这也不是多莉帕顿
There is no world tour, and this is not Dolly Parton.
好的, 看, 看, 这些实际上是...
Okay, look. Look, these are absolutely...
你在干...? 她在干什么? 弄疼我了!
What are you...? What is she doing? That hurts!
- 你为什么要跑?  - 某个疯女人要追我!
-Why did you run?  -Some crazy woman was chasing me!
抱歉, 抱歉, 帕顿小姐 "你再来一次"是我的婚礼歌曲
Excuse me, excuse me. Miss Parton, "Here You Come Again" was my wedding song.
- 我很爱你  - 甜心, 别打扰帕顿小姐
-I just love you.  -Honey, let's leave Miss Parton alone.
我也很爱那首歌 那是首很棒的歌!
I love that song too. That was an amazing song!
-你为什么还在我身上?
Why are you on top of me?
我只是个大歌迷
I'm just a big fan.
这也在CNN...
It's also on CNN...
...MSNBC...
...和半岛电视台播出了
...and Al Jazeera.
- 我想问她 些关于...  - 你真的认为你很特别嘛
-I was trying to question her regarding...  -You really think you're something special.
我有75个人日日夜夜地 为这个案子忙着...
I have got 75 people working on this case day and night...
- ...但是他们加起来也不如你, 是吗?  - 那个豪华轿车司机...
-...and they don't stack up to you, do they?  -The limo driver...
我需要你别插手这个案子
I want you off this case.
好吧, 我很抱歉, 长官, 但是你没 权利让我离开这个案子
Well, I am sorry, sir, but you don't have the authority to kick me off this case.
我能打电话给指挥官 他是我很亲密的私人朋友
I could call the director, who happens to be a close, personal friend.
活着我还能打给总统 他还邀请我去他家做客
Or I could even call the president, who invited me to dinner at his house.
我想我们知道我说的是谁的家 是吗? 那是白宫
And I think we know which house I'm talking about, don't we? It's white.
事实上, 那像蛋壳, 如果你...
Actually, it's eggshell, if you...
我是拉斯维加斯分局指挥官 在我辖区内我就有权力
I am the SAC in Las Vegas. I have authority over my territory.
而且当指挥官在国家电台 看见了你...
And when the director sees you on national television...
...这样对待他最喜欢西部乡村歌手 也会站在我这边的
...nose -tackling his favorite country -western singer, he will back me up.
现在, 我想要你们俩今天 乘上飞机回纽约去
Now, I want the two of you on a jet back to New York today.
你认为你能处理好这个 小小的任务吗, 富尔曼?
Do you think you can handle that tiny, little task, Foreman?
当然, 长官
Of course, sir.
好的, 我给你们买到了 这趟飞机的最后三个座位
Okay. I got you the last three seats on the flight.
珍妮, 帕姆, 你们只能坐下趟了, 抱歉
Janine, Pam, you have to take the next one. Sorry.
- 因为我们仅仅是做头发和化妆的?  - 我们能去酒吧
-Because we're just hair and makeup?  -We could go to the bar.
去五个小时?
For five hours?
好啦
Okay.
指挥官将会在任何时候回电的
The director's gonna call me back any minute.
好的, 当他回电了...
Good. And when he does...
...你可以告诉他追赶多莉  是你一个人的蠢主意
...you can let him know that chasing Dolly was all your dumb idea.
哦, 是吗? 好的, 让我来问你点事情 饶舌的卡蒂
Oh, really? Well, let me ask you something, Chatty Cathy.
这是怎么回事, 是谁说得 "团队, 唷, 你和我在一起"?
What happened to, "Team, yo. You and me in it together"?
再也不了, 这是在 你毁了我的前途之前
Don't do that again. And that was before you ruined my career.
- 什么?  - 是的
-What?  -Yeah.
麦克唐纳说如果我把这次任务搞砸了
McDonald said that if I screwed this up,
我就要离开局里了, 谢谢你, 哈特
then I'm out of the Bureau. Thanks, Hart.
你在抱怨什么呐? 你有不是很出名
What are you complaining about? You're not famous.
没人知道你是谁, 这只是你个人的失败
Nobody knows who you are. You're a private failure.
但是你看我? 你看我? 每个人都认识我
But you see this? You see this? Everybody knows this.
所以如果我搞砸了, 我就是失败的脸了
So if I screw up, I'm failure face.
好的, 把你那张失败的脸从我这张 被毁了前途的脸移开...
Well, get your failure face out of my ruined -career face...
...因为现在我疯了 我很生气和疯了, 所以...
...because right now I'm mad, and I'm pissed off and mad, so...
哦, 好的, 打住 所以你是两个"疯了"
Oh, okay, hold on. So you're double mad?
那么我就是 疯了, 疯了, 疯了, 好吗? 比你多一个
then I am mad, mad, mad. All right? Top that one.
- 住嘴!  - 你必须停止打我...
-Back off!  -You gotta stop hitting me...
...因为你每次这样做, 都会起皱纹的!
...because every time you do, it wrinkles!
女士们, 女士们!
Ladies, ladies!
冷静, 坐下, 坐下 我要分开你们俩
Calm down. Sit down. Sit down. I'm gonna separate the two of you.
疯了, 疯了, 疯了, 疯了, 四个
Mad, mad, mad, mad. Four.
我还是想开枪打她
I can still shoot her from here.
那你必须先绕过我才能靠近她
You have to lean over me to get to her.
现在, 让我们冷静然后试着看看 积极的一面, 我们都很健康
Now, let's calm down and try to focus on the positive. We have our health.
- 你们必须长途飞行数公里  - 富尔曼, 刚才你说了什么?
-You'll be getting frequent -flyer miles.  -Foreman, what did you just say?
长途飞行数公里, 要升级是很困难的
Frequent -flyer miles. It's a great way to get upgrades.
不, 你说她...
No, you said that she...
你说她必须那她必须先 绕过你才能靠近我
You said that she would have to lean over you to get to me.
看看绑匪们做了些什么
Look at what the kidnappers are doing.
这群人绕过了谢丽尔去接近斯坦
This guy is leaning over Cheryl to get to Stan.
他们为什么那么做 如果他们的目标是谢丽尔?
Why would they do that if they were after Cheryl?
好的, 看这个, 看这个 他们几乎都没碰她
Okay, and look at this. Look at this. They're not even touching her.
不, 她被夹在了里面 就像是谢丽尔三明治, 她...她...
No, she's just stuck in there, like a little Cheryl sandwich. She's... She's...
哦, 上帝, 她抓住了他们 我教过她这招
Oh, my God. She is grabbing them. I taught her that wristlock.
- 她不是在自我防御, 她是...  - 她是在保护斯坦
-She's not defending herself. She's...  -She's defending Stan.
也许他们的目标不是谢丽尔 也许他们的目标是斯坦
Maybe they weren't after Cheryl. Maybe they were after Stan.
这个男人不会唱歌 难道这也是罪过吗?
The man can't sing, but is that a crime?
- 这就是我们要找出的东西  - 嗨, 看, 他们登机了
-That's what we're gonna find out.  -Hey, look, they're boarding.
- 让它去吧, 哈特  - 哦, 福勒, 回来
-Let it go, Hart.  -Oh, Fuller, come on.
醒醒, 闻闻冰焦糖玛奇雅朵咖啡 你知道的我在说什么
Wake up and smell the iced Venti Caramel Macchiato. You know I'm onto something.
- 好的, 告诉科林斯吧  - 我们争吵过, 他不会听我的
-Okay. Tell Collins.  -We have issues. He won't listen to me.
- 那你认为我会吗?  - 是的, 是的, 我认为你会
-And you think I am?  -Yes. Yes, I do.
你知道, 你不会开始旅程 除非你们登机了, 所以快
You know, you don't get your miles unless you're actually on the flight, so come on.
- 你是孤立的, 哈特  - 不, 我不是
-You're on your own, Hart.  -No, I'm not.
因为虽然你拒绝打扮或者修眉...
Because even though you refuse to dress up or separate those eyebrows...
...你也不能否认你有自己的风格
...you cannot deny that you have a style.
灰色套装, 白色衬衫, 男性袜子 你是FBI探员
Gray suit, white shirt, masculine shoes. You are an FBl agent.
而这是你拥有的一切
And that is all that you have.
就像你所说得, 如果你现在回去了 你就会被总局炒了
And like you said, if you go back there now, you are out of the Bureau.
现在去纽约624号航班在所有通道检票
Now boarding all rows on flight 624 to New York.
福勒, 我求你了
Fuller, I am begging you.
你能知道这对我有多么痛苦吗?
Do you have any idea how painful this is for me?
通常, 这种痛苦是需要麻醉才能减轻的
Usually, they give an epidural for this kind of agony.
福勒, 求求你, 只是...只是, 求求你
Fuller, please, just.... Just, please.
哈特, 你最好是对的, 否则我发誓...
Hart, you better be right, or I swear...
你会踢我的瘦小屁股还会毁我的容 我知道
You're gonna kick my skinny white ass and break my face. I know.
我已经付了钱买票了 如果你们不登机, 我不能报销的
I already paid for the seats, and I don't get reimbursed unless you're on the flight.
我让你们在这过夜是因为我想 看着你们
I'm letting you spend the night because I wanna keep my eyes on you.
- 明天, 你们必须上飞机  - 好的. 我们会尽快回家的
-Tomorrow, you guys are on a flight.  -Okay, as soon as we go to the home.
- 谁的家?  - 斯坦费尔特妈妈住的地方
-Whose home?  -Where Stan Fields' mother lives.
她是最后一个见到他的人 也许她知道些什么
She was the last person to see him. Maybe she knows something.
你被认为在纽约了, 你是名人 每个人都可能认出你
You're supposed to be in New York. You're famous. Everyone there will recognize you.
别担心, 祖尔会给我改装的
Not to worry. Joel will come up with something to make us blend.
- 他是天生的易容师  - 我不相信
-He's a born blender.  -I don't believe this.
你们很幸运 因为今天珍妮特要加班...
You guys are lucky that Janet had to work late...
...如果她在这, 她会忍受不了 你们中间的任何一个
...because if she was here, she would not put up with any of this.
现在, 珍妮特...珍妮特在做紧急任务
Now, Janet... Janet runs a tight ship.
我爱在维加斯购物
I love shopping in Vegas.
- 还有什么地方可以 找到24小时的假发? - 好了, 开始工作
- Where else can you find a 24-hour wiggery? - Well, to work.
嗨! 嗨! 那是我的房间! 嗨!
Hey, hey! That's my room! Hey!
嗨!
Hey!
- 我从没想到  - 什么?
-I never would have suspected.  -What?
你是挑剔的旅行枕头类型
You as a dainty -travel -pillow type.
- 那是低过敏的  - 哦, 是吗?
-It's hypoallergenic.  -Oh, really?
- 那你过敏什么?  - 除了你?
-And what are you allergic to?  -Besides you?
贝类, 猫, 狗, 和任何脏脏的动物...
Shellfish, cats, dogs, any type of animal dander...
...乳制品, 灰尘...
...dairy products, dust...
- 你应该生活在塑料泡里  - 塑料也过敏
-You should be in a plastic bubble.  -Plastic.
- 那就能说得通了  - 说得通什么?
-That explains it.  -Explains what?
- 未为什么你这么容易生气  - 我没易怒, 我只是过敏
-Why you're so angry.  -I'm not angry, I'm allergic.
我说就是, 你知道...
All I was saying was that it just, you know...
...不可能一直和生病的小孩和睦相处
...couldn't have been easy being a kid sick like that all the time.
我的意思是, 没可能 没有狗或者猫或者冰淇淋或者灰尘的
I mean, not being able to have a dog or a cat or ice cream or dust.
那很好呀
It wasn't bad.
- 是吗?  - 那我又要来说说我的爸爸了
-Really?  -I got to hang out with my dad a lot.
他是个体育记者, 所以他看电视 播放的每场比赛
He was a sportswriter, so we got to watch all the games on TV together...
...然后教我拳击
...and he taught me how to box.
教我如何照顾自己
Taught me how to take care of myself.
好的, 我确信他很为你自豪
Well, I'm sure he was very proud of you.
什么?
Was?
是的, 我看了你的档案 你是非常想要成为一名探员的
Yeah, I read on your file that he died before you became an agent.
- 你看了我的档案?  - 我想要确定你不是疯子
-You read my file?  -I had to make sure you weren't crazy.
是的, 结果表明你不能相信档案
Yeah. Turns out you can't trust a file.
是的, 好的, 我觉得你是不能相信它
Yeah, well, I guess you can't.
我本认为我会喜欢一个穿着运动服的 假小子的, 她的妈妈是个探员
I thought I would've liked a tough tomboy from Jersey whose mom was an agent.
- 你看了我的档案? 更糟
-You read my file?  -Worse.
你的书
Your book.
必须确认你不是疯子
Had to make sure you weren't crazy.
结果表明, 你不能相信书
Turns out you can't trust a book.
是的, 他们只出版...
Yeah, they brought in this writer...
...能成功地把整个故事变成童话 的作者的书
...who managed to turn the entire story into some fairy tale.
在第一稿中, 他搞成了 我妈妈的去世好像...
In the first draft, he made it sound like my mother died...
...是为了独立挽救国家, 但是事实是, 你知道嘛, 只是...
...single -handedly saving the country, when all it was was just, you know, a...
只是药物反应
It was just a drug bust gone bad.
抱歉
Sorry.
抱歉提了你的父亲
Sorry about your dad.
但是我真的很抱歉你读了那本书
But I'm mostly sorry you had to read that book.
但是, 我喜欢里面的照片
I like the pictures, though.
哦, 是吗?
Oh, really?
是的, 特别是那个和一个小伙子的合影 他叫什么名字?
Yeah, especially that one with that guy. What was his name?
哪个?
Which one?
那个探员, 那个在庆典的时候 和你在一起的
The agent, the one that was in the pageant with you.
艾瑞克 马休斯
Eric Matthews.
是的, 他很火辣
Yeah. He was hot.
我想是的
I guess.
晚安, 哈特
Night, Hart.
晚安, 福勒
Good night, Fuller.
富尔曼, 我们在接近目标
Foreman, we're in. Approaching target.
欢迎来威望救助中心 能帮你什么吗?
Welcome to Prestige Assisted Living. How can I help you?
嗨, 我是祖尔 弗莱敏 这是我的妈妈
Hi, I'm Joel Flammenbaum, and this is my mother.
艾德. 艾德 弗莱敏, 你好吗? 这是我的可爱护士, 罗茜
Ida. Ida Flammenbaum. How are you? This is my lovely nurse, Rosie.
- 你好  - 她不是很会交际
-Hello.  -She's not very social...
...但是如果你感觉吃多了 她会一种很好的灌肠法
...but she gives a superb enema if you're feeling a little clogged up.
你有兴趣参观我们的设施吗?
Are you interested in touring our facilities?
哦, 是的, 我们很感兴趣 我迫不及待地想要摆脱她
Oh, yes, we are very interested. I can't wait to get rid of her.
哦, 不要听他的, 他是妈妈地乖儿子 过来, 让我来帮你整整领带
Oh, don't you listen to him. He's a mama's boy. Come here, cutie. Let me fix your tie.
- 他是个好孩子  - 妈妈, 现在别
-He's such a mama's boy.  -Mom, not now.
现在, 这就是乖儿子的脸 乖儿子的脸
Now, that is a mama's boy's face. That's a mama's boy's face.
你们有安乐死计划吗?
Do you have a euthanasia program?
我们只需要填一些表格 如果你需要的话 请等我一会
We just need to fill out some forms. If you'll just give me one minute.
别让那个招待员闲下来
Keep the receptionist busy.
我们要去问些问题 假定我们能找到听的到的人
We're gonna ask some questions, assuming we can find anyone that can hear.
拿着我的钱包, 我们走吧, 罗茜
Hold my purse. Let's roll, Rosie.
你好, 我是埃德弗莱敏, 我是新来的
Hello there. I'm Ida Flammenbaum. I am new.
好的, 我不是新人
Well, I'm not new.
- 那么你是?  - 巴斯特哈里森
-And you are?  -Buster Harrison.
哦, 巴斯特, 那是真的吗, 斯坦费尔特的 母亲也住在这里?
Oh, Buster. Is it true that Stan Fields' mother is residing here?
是的, 她就在那儿
Yes, she's right over there.
卡罗尔? 这是艾德, 她想要见你
Carol? This is Ida. She wanted to meet you.
哦, 巴斯特, 哦, 巴斯特, 我很抱歉 给巴斯特我最喜欢的足部按摩
Oh, Buster. Oh, Buster, I'm so sorry. Give Buster one of your famous foot massages.
嗨, 当我按摩的时候 你觉得我最著名的灌肠法怎样
Hey. While I'm at it, how about one of my famous enemas?
你能一天搞定两个?
Can you get two of them in a day?
菲尔兹女士 菲尔兹女士
Mrs. Fields, Mrs. Fields.
听上去像是小甜点, 这很有趣
Sounds like the cookie. It's very funny.
在你听了30年之后 就不会这么觉得了, 艾德
Not after you've heard it for 30 years, Ida.
我很肯定, 我只是想过来...
I'm sure. I just wanted to come over here...
...告诉你我很抱歉关于绑架的事情
...and tell you how very sorry I am about the kidnapping.
哦, 是的, 可怜的, 可怜的斯坦
Oh, yeah, poor, poor Stanley.
但是他活该
But he had it coming.
是吗?
Really?
是的, 每个人都说他是那么受人尊敬
Well, from what I hear from everyone, he's such a mensch.
我的意思是, 谁会伤害他呢?
I mean, who would wanna hurt him?
你知道嘛, 他喜欢荡妇
Well, you know, he loved the sluts.
卡罗尔发音不准
把Slot(老虎机)说成Slut(荡妇)
他喜欢荡妇?
He loved the sluts?
- 荡妇!  - 荡妇
-The sluts!  -The sluts.
- 赌博机  - 赌博机
-The slut machines.  -Slot machines.
当他不主持庆典的时候, 他就在 这儿, 拉斯维加斯, 赌博
When he wasn't doing that pageant, he was here in Vegas, gambling.
我不知道他拿到表了
I don't know where he gets that from.
所以你是说...你是说 你的儿子喜欢赌博机
So you were saying... You were saying that your son, he loves the slot machines.
我求他不要玩了, 我对他说:
I begged him to stop. I said to him:
"总有一天, 赌博会带给你大麻烦的"
"One of these days, gambling's gonna get you in a lot of trouble."
我借给她600美元, 再也没拿回来过
I lent him 600 bucks, I never got it back.
我真想打断他的腿, 但是我是他的母亲
I was ready to break his legs, and I'm his mother.
那就只能等放高利贷的抓他了
Wait till the loan sharks get ahold of him.
放高利贷的总会找到你 他们非常...
The loan sharks every time will get you. They're very...
放高利贷的
Loan shark.
- 是放高利贷的  -艾德, 你能走了
-It's the loan sharks.  -Ida, you can walk!
- 赞美上帝!  - 摩西
-Praise Jesus!  -Moses.
摩西, 我又能走路了 我要签了这个地方
Moses, I am walking again. Sign me up for this place.
我爱这里, 这里的男人也让我很愉快
I love it here, and the men make me all fakakta.
杰夫, 为什么我们来这?
Jeff, why are we here?
- 因为我们有任务, 格雷西  - 好的, 看
-Because we had a deal, Gracie.  -Okay, look.
任务就像珍珠, 它们很美 但是它们始终会碎
Deals are like pearls. They're lovely, but they fall apart all the time.
我把你的行礼打包了 我们这就去机场
I'm grabbing your luggage. We're going to the airport.
难道你没听见斯坦的妈妈说什么了吗?
Didn't you hear what Stan's mother said?
是的, 我听到了, "荡妇" 我就下来了, 好吗?
Yes, I did. "Sluts." I wrote it down, all right?
"放高利贷的"那就是为什么我们 必须回到局里...
"Loan shark." That's why we have to get back to the Bureau...
...然后打印出所有维加斯的 放高利贷的名单
...do a CHC printout of every loan shark in Vegas.
你不能去局里 你被认为已经在纽约了
You can't go to the Bureau. You are supposed to be in New York.
这就是为什么要你去 你能去...
And that is why you can go and you can take...
- 不! 不!  - 好的, 看着, 杰夫...
-No! No!  -Okay, look, Jeff...
...我喜欢用我的枪, 除非是出于自卫 或者确实需要...
...l don't like to use my gun unless it's in self -defense or at a really good sale...
...但是如果你不回去打印名单的话 我就不得不...
...but if you don't go back and get those CHCs, I have to...
你知道的, 我必须开枪
You know, I have to shoot you.
你不会的, 格雷西
You won't do it, Gracie.
这就是我所喜欢的 学习如何共同工作
This is what I like. Learning to work together.
小小的"黑檀木与白象牙"剧目
A little "Ebony & Ivory" action.
- 伙计们, 我干不了  - 别拖泥带水的, 富尔曼, 像个男人
-Guys, I can't do it.  -Stop being a wuss, Foreman. Be a man!
是的, 像福勒那样
Yeah, like Fuller.
好的, 干完了然后我们就去机场 这已经足够足够了
Okay. But this is it. Then we're going to the airport. Enough's enough.
- 绝对不  - 我坚决反对
-Absolutely. Okay.  -I'm putting my foot down.
他坚决反对
He's putting his foot down.
拿些高清晰的带子 再录一卷录像带,价再高点
Got some high -def tapes for the new ransom video. More production value.
哥...
Bro...
...也许我们应该住手了
...maybe we should get out now.
你开玩笑吗? 在我们需要的时候 我们抓到了他们, 他们现在很紧张
Are you kidding? We got them where we want them. They're getting nervous.
但是如果他们不答应 我们的条件, 我们...
But if they don't agree to our demands, we...
那就是我们为什么要录个新的
That's why we're making a new one.
我们要让美国小姐说 我们提前的最终期限
We're gonna have Miss United States say we're moving up the deadline.
或者今晚把现金汇到 国外银行帐户或者就她死
And either we get our cash wired to an offshore account tonight, or she's dead.
那么, 我们怎么做? 射死他们?
So, what do we do? Shoot them?
不, 我们杀死他们然后 去旅馆拿小小的报酬
No. We're gonna kill them and get a little payback at the hotel.
你知道维加斯的位置, 对吗?
You know how location is everything in Vegas, right?
当我们干完这个后 宝藏岛就变成了巨大的丑陋的犯罪地点
Well, after we pull this off, Treasure Island's gonna be a big, ugly crime site.
- 什么, 我们就这样进去吗?  - 不
-What, are we just gonna drive in?  -No.
在演出开始前, 我们把他们 捆起来放在船底
Just before the show starts, we'll tie them up at the bottom of the boat.
然后把船沉了, 再见, 美国小姐
That ship sinks, so long, Miss United States.
- 嗨, 伙计们  - 富尔曼
-Hey, guys.  -Foreman.
多莉帕顿那事做的不错
Nice job with Dolly Parton.
是的, 我们注意多莉 很长时间了 但是是你最终把她带进来了
Yeah. We've been after Dolly for a long time, but it took you to finally bring her in.
- 我做不到  - 不, 你能行
-I can't do this.  -Yes, you can.
记住路易威登说得 "那都在包里", 你能做到
Remember what Louis Vuitton said, "lt's in the bag." You can do this.
好的
Okay.
他做不到
He can't do this.
像一个胖女人喝醉了那样走下去
Going down like a fat woman on a greased fire pole.
我听到了
I heard that.
我进入了数据库
I'm going into the database.
- 太棒了, 保持联络  - 好的
-Great. Just keep us filled in.  -Okay.
某人在键盘旁边留下了一罐苏打水
Someone left a can of soda by the keyboard.
我出了很多汗
I'm sweating profusely.
我想我忘记关烘箱了
I think I left my oven on.
- 我们开始打印了  - 太了不起了, 杰夫, 太棒了, 你做到了
-We're printing.  -Awesome, Jeff. Awesome. You did it.
- 福勒输了赌注  - 那还没结束
-Fuller just lost a bet.  -Not over yet.
- 科林斯探员, 请回答...  - 科林斯探员!
-Agent Collins, if you could just answer a...  -Agent Collins!
好的, 这将是最后一个问题, 你, 请
All right, this is gonna be the last question. Yes, go ahead.
如果明天的最终限期到了怎么办...
What happens if tomorrow's deadline comes and goes...
...这个案子就没进展吗?
...and there's no break in the case?
我们正在和庆典组织方会话 我们还没谈判成功
We've spoken with the pageant administration. We will not negotiate.
他们有一个选择, 让弗雷泽小姐和 菲尔兹先生自由, 这就是了
They have one choice, and that is to free Miss Frazier and Mr. Fields, and that's it.
- 不在提问, 谢谢  - 只是再问一个问题
-No more questions. Thank you.  -Just one more question!
- 那不对  - 什么不对
-That's not right.  -What's not right?
不, 一定是身高
No. It must be the height.
- 杰夫, 杰夫, 怎么啦? 怎么啦?  - 是珍妮特
-Jeff. Jeff, what's up? What's up?  -It's Janet.
我不确定, 但是我想她和...
I'm not sure, but I think she's with....
和什么? 和你?
With what? With you?
你证据? 和孩子? 和什么?
With holding evidence? With child? With what?
和什么?!
With what?!
和科林斯
With Collins.
富尔曼!
Foreman!
富尔曼
Foreman.
- 你拿着打印表干吗?  - 那是和美国小姐的案子有关
-What are you doing with CHCs?  -They're for the Miss United States case.
- 那案子怎么了?  - 你们两个刚刚...?
-What about that case?  -Were the two of you just...?
杰夫, 冷静! 好嘛, 你只要出来
Jeff, chill! Okay, you've just gotta get out of there.
富尔曼, 你为什么有这些警察局档案?
Foreman, why do you have those rap sheets?
一个普通的数据库检查 看看有什么值得怀疑的对象
A general database check to see if there were any suspects worth pursuing.
我只是做一个普通的数据库检查 看看有什么值得怀疑的对象
I was doing a general database check to see if there were any suspects worth pursuing.
你们两个刚刚...?
Were you two just...?
这不是普通的数据库检查 这是对放高利贷的重罪特殊搜索
This isn't a general database check. This is a felony -specific search for loan sharks.
说你注意到绑架录像带...
Say you noticed on the kidnapping video...
...绑匪想要绑架斯坦费尔特
...the assailants were attempting to abduct Stan Fields.
- 富尔曼, 我要个答案  - 再说一遍
-Foreman, I want an answer.  -Say it again.
我要个答案
I want an answer.
- 在绑架录像带上, 绑匪...  - 你怎么了?
-On the kidnapping video, the assailants...  -What is wrong with you?
- 说快点  - 你怎么了?
-Say it faster.  -What's wrong with you?
绑匪试图绑架斯坦费尔特...
The assailants were attempting to abduct Stan Fields...
...而你发现斯坦费尔特 有严重的债务问题, 水
...and you found out that Stan Fields had a gambling problem. Water.
我发现绑匪试图绑架斯坦费尔特...
I saw the assailants attempting to abduct Stan Fields...
...所以我追查这个线索, 发现他有严重的债务问题
...so I pursued the matter and found out he has a gambling problem.
你追查线索? 谁授权的?
You pursued the matter further? Under whose authority?
- 你说谎了, 富尔曼  - 富尔曼, 我在等你的回答
-You've gotta lie, Foreman.  -Foreman, I am waiting.
告诉他我发晕了 把一个嫌疑犯的头按在了墙上...
Tell him that I'm dizzy from smashing a suspect's head into the wall...
...然后就不记得了 这通常能起作用
...and I can't remember. That always works.
你知道我想做什么吗? 晕倒
You know what I like to do? Faint.
我们不能这么做, 他很诚实
We can't do this, guys. He's honest.
- 杰夫, 告诉他实情?  - 实情?
-Jeff, tell him the truth.  -The truth?
- 你确定吗?  - 我确定我要真相?
-Are you sure?  -Am I sure I want the truth?
富尔曼, 我想你去作个X射线扫描
Foreman, I want you to get a CAT scan.
我没得到这个信息 是哈特和福勒探员得到的
I didn't get this information. Agents Hart and Fuller did.
- 什么? 他们应该在纽约  - 好吧, 在机场...
-How? They're in New York.  -Well, at the airport...
他们不在纽约
They're not in New York.
哈特?
Hart?
- 是的, 长官  - 我猜福勒探员和你在一起
-Yes, sir.  -I assume that Agent Fuller is with you.
- 是的, 长官  - 还有祖尔
-Yes, sir.  -And Joel.
你好, 沃尔特
Hello, Walter.
我要你们全部马上到报告室来
I want all of you in the situation room now.
- 这就是我确实想要的, 那是对了  - 长官
-That is exactly what I want. That's right.  -Sir.
我只想让你知道这和富尔曼探员无关
I want you to know that none of this was Agent Foreman's idea.
哦, 我知道, 我知道 因为富尔曼没有任何主意的
Oh, I know, I know. Because Foreman doesn't have any ideas.
这是你需要把整件事写下来, 哈特
This has you written all over it, Hart.
你总是按照自己的方法行事, 是吗?
You've really gotta do things your way, don't you?
杜嘉班纳(Dolce & Gabbana)公司
位于意大利米兰
是奢侈品领域中
最主要的国际集团之一
杜嘉班纳总是说 我们需要我们自己的行事风格, 长官
Dolce and Gabbana always said we should express our own personal style, sir.
- 他们说到了防弹衣...  - 你不是超人探员
-They were talking about a vest...  -You're no super agent.
你只是瞎猫遇见死耗子了
You're just a loose cannon who lucked into being in the right place at the right time.
你不必这样残酷地对她, 她是...
You don't have to be that hard on her. She was...
哦, 我很高兴你站在她那边, 福勒...
Oh, I am so glad you're with her on this, Fuller...
...因为你们俩要一起走, 即刻生效
...because you two are going down together. The works.
- 复习登机, 部门的听力...  - 长官, 我们通过电邮又收到了消息
-Review board, departmental hearings...  -Sir, we got another message e -mailed.
给我看
Show me.
- 放  - 这是谢丽尔弗雷泽
-Play it.  -This is Cheryl Frazier.
你好, 再次
Hi, again.
最终限期改变了, 不是明天了 改在今晚了
The deadline has been changed. It's not tomorrow, it's tonight.
绑匪已经把指令传真给庆典主办方了...
The kidnappers are going to fax instructions to the pageant...
...他们需要支付500万美元
...where the 5 million should be sent.
如果他们没收到钱, 我就要死了
And if they don't receive it, I'm going to be dead.
"Booty"有赃物或屁股的含义
我知道这是一大笔钱 但是现在是我的屁股处于危险了
And I know it's a lot of money, but it's my booty on the line.
- 所以...  - 这是斯坦费尔特...
-So....  -This is Stan Fields...
...对于死来说, 她太年轻了
...and she's too young to die.
而我也没看上去那么年纪大, 所以请赎我们
And I'm not as old as I look. So please.
我们还得到了这个, 长官
We also got this, sir.
一个打印店的店员看见一个可疑男子 在一个小时钱电邮了信息
A clerk at a print store saw a suspicious man e -mail a message about an hour ago.
空中监控发现一辆小型卡车 和绑架录像带中的车辆吻合的...
Aerial spotted a pickup truck matching the vehicle in the kidnapping video...
-...正向南以15的速度  - 你看这个?
-...heading south on 1 5.  -You see this?
这是真正的信息 不是多莉帕顿和老人之家
This is real information. Not Dolly Parton and senior homes.
这就是我们维加斯的做法
That's how we do it in Vegas.
我需要在I-15设置路障 同时增加空中监控力度
I want roadblocks on I-15 and increased surveillance at the airports.
- 富尔曼?  - 是的, 长官
-Foreman?  -Yes, sir.
我想要你把哈特探员, 福勒探员 和祖尔送上回纽约的飞机
I want you to put agents Hart, Fuller and Joel on the first flight back to New York.
为了确保没问题, 这次奥肯和希尔斯 将和你同行
To make sure there's no problem, Okun and Hills will be going with you.
如果这次你在出错, 你就被解雇了 你还会犯吗?
And if you get it wrong this time, you are fired. Do you copy?
那没必要吧, 因为没人会被解雇 没人会要离开
That won't be necessary, because nobody is getting fired, and nobody is leaving.
你又错了, 哈特!
Wrong again, Hart!
如果我再在这个城市看见你 你就可以忘了登机了
And if I ever see you in my city again, you can forget about the review board.
我会以妨碍司法公正逮捕你的...
I will have you arrested for obstruction of justice...
...你就可以在拉斯维加斯待很长的 一段时间了, 不过是在监狱
...and you can spend a very long time in Las Vegas, in a jail cell.
我已经受够了你的粗鲁, 迟钝和古龙水
I have really had just about enough of your rudeness and insensitivity and cologne.
哦, 是吗? 那你想要做什么? 打电话给指挥官吗?
Oh, really? And what are you gonna do about it? Call the director?
继续, 我已经给他挂过电话了 你猜他说什么?
Go ahead. I got off the phone with him. Know what he said?
他说你是他犯的最大的错误
He said that you are the biggest mistake he ever made.
他还说, 我引用的...
And he said, and I quote...
..你是"开始成为局里的债务和困窘"
...that you "have become a liability and an embarrassment to the Bureau."
现在, 走吧
Now, get going.
奥肯
Okun.
是科林斯, 是的, 长官, 我们在机场
It's Collins. Yes, sir, we're at the airport.
- 他对我发火了吗?  - 对不起, 长官, 我听不到你
-Is he mad at me?  -Sorry, sir, I'm losing you.
- 他想要和我说话吗?  - 富尔曼! 离开我!
-Does he wanna talk to me?  -Foreman! Leave him alone!
现在登机, 航班624飞往纽约
Now boarding, flight 624 to New York.
是的, 我看到了你的广告...
Yeah. I was looking at your ad...
...我在想你有多莉帕顿的模仿者嘛
...and I was wondering if you have a Dolly Parton performer.
没有?
No?
好的
Okay.
哈特, 也许关于多莉 你是对的 可许我们只是找错了多莉
Hart, maybe you were right about Dolly. Maybe you just had the wrong Dolly.
- 你不知道他们是否有多莉   - 他们没有
-You don't know if they have a Dolly.  -They don't.
我刚刚打电话了 他们说仅有的一个在维加斯...
I just called there, and they said the only place in Vegas...
...在绿洲龙酒吧有个 多莉帕顿的模仿者
...that has a Dolly Parton performer is the Oasis Drag Club.
上飞机吧, 福勒
Just get on the plane, Fuller.
- 你还想救谢丽尔不?  - 我可能会害死她
-Do you wanna save Cheryl or not?  -I'm gonna get her killed.
你怎么了? 那个庆典上的女孩发生了什么?
What's up with you? What happened to that girl from the pageant?
她走了
She's gone.
她的男朋友, 艾瑞克 马休斯和她 分手了, 彻底地分手
Her boyfriend, Eric Matthews, broke up with her, and it was absolutely devastating.
这就是你发生的事情?
Is that what happened to you?
哦, 那很可惜, 来吧
Oh, that's pathetic. Come on.
很多人和我分了手 你只要痛打他们一顿然后继续前进
Plenty of guys have broken up with me. You just beat them up and move on.
只有你和富尔曼搞得和肥皂剧一样
Only you and Foreman turn it into some big soap opera.
是的, 当然你不会懂得杰夫的感受 因为他不是一个机器人
Well. Of course you don't understand how Jeff feels, because he's not a cyborg.
他知道拒绝和羞辱的滋味
He knows what it feels like to be rejected and humiliated.
感觉你的行被剖开...
To feel your heart ripped open...
...因为你最后给了一个机会弥补 你们的关系...
...because you finally took a chance on that relationship...
...但是那只证实了你的恐惧...
...and it wound up confirming your worst fears...
...你是没有价值的, 你不值得关心
...that you are worthless and not worth caring about.
所以你不会明白杰夫的感受
So you may not understand, but that is how Jeff feels.
马休斯甩了是对的
Matthews was right to dump you.
- 收回你的话  - 我说"你迫使我呀", 但你不行
-Take that back.  -I would say, "Make me," but you can't.
好的
Okay.
好的...
All right. Well...
...现在我有两件事要说
...then I just have two things to say.
- 什么?  - 第一, 我们在公共场合...
-What?  -First of all, we are in a public place...
...所以我们要表现得理智一点 第二点...
...so we have to display a sense of decorum, and second of all...
...我可以打破这个原则
...l might break a nail.
收回去吧! 收回去
Take it back! Take it back.
呀!
Jeez!
所有科林斯说的话都是垃圾
All the stuff that Collins said back there was a bunch of bull.
你指出那个豪华轿车司机有问题
You figured out the limo driver was dirty.
你指出他们的目标是斯坦
You figured out that they were after Stan.
你不是碰运气, 你是靠实力
You're not lucky. You're good.
谢谢, 但是还是要收回那句话 收回, 收回
Thank you. But take it back, take it back, take it back.
好的, 我收回, 只要你承认一件事 我就收回
Okay, I'll take it back. I'll take it back if you admit one thing.
哦, 上帝!
Oh, God!
这是你第一次表现得像格雷西 哈特
For the first time in a long time, you feel like the real Gracie Hart.
哦, 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
变形的肌肉会切断空气供应的
Straining muscles cutting off someone's air supply.
像猪一样出汗
Sweating like a pig.
你是对的, 我有感觉像个女人了
You're right, I feel like a woman again.
好的, 我收回, 现在放手
Good. I take it back. Now release.
你先
You first.
- 三下  - 一
-On three.  -One.
二, 三
Two. Three.
哦, 不
Oh, no.
好的, 只要表现出你相信我
Okay, just to show you I trust you.
现在所有乘坐624航班 飞往纽约的旅客请登机
Now boarding all passengers for flight 624 to New York.
谢谢
Thanks.
没事
All right.
好的, 孩子们, 马戏团是时候离开了
Okay, kids, time for the circus to leave town.
来吧, 女孩们
Come on, girls.
我们要怎样摆脱这些家伙?
How are we gonna get rid of these guys?
我不知道, 这要很狡猾
I don't know. But it has to be subtle.
继续走
Keep it moving.
上帝!
God!
老天爷
Lordy!
女士的生理问题
Ladies' time.
我抽筋了, 我必须...必须 去趟洗手间
I have the cramps. I have to... I have to go to the bathroom.
要上飞机了
There's one on the plane.
我知道, 但是, 伙计们, 经痛对我来说 是件了不起的大事, 所以我要...
I know, but, guys, PMS for me means "pants might shred," so I gotta...
- 忘了吧, 哈特 伙计们, 你们不能理解, 我肿胀了
-Forget it, Hart.  -Guys, you don't understand. I bloat.
我喝了水, 我膨胀了, 我会 改变机舱的压力
I take on water, and I expand, and I may change the cabin pressure of that plane.
我带她去洗手间
I gotta take her to the bathroom.
- 我需要止血垫  - 你们听到了嘛, 我们有个探员倒下了
-I need a tampon!  -You heard her, we got a agent down.
我们需要止血垫!
We need tampons!
- 我不去买那个  - 我都不给老婆买这个
-I'm not getting those.  -I don't do it for my wife.
这是个真正男人的任务 需要什么指定的牌子吗?
This is a job for a real man. Any particular brand?
- 都可以  - 珍妮特喜欢那种装在蓝盒子里的
-Any brand.  -Janet liked the ones in the blue box...
...上面还有雏菊的
...with the daisies on it.
你真的不明白吗? 有事要发生了
You're really not following this, are you? Something's up.
止血垫
Tampons.
给他们一点时间
Give them a couple minutes.
零 -一, 你看到什么?
Zero -one, what do you got?
- 没有动静, 适合行动  - 记下来, 格里芬, 开始行动
-No movement. Good to go.  -Copy that. Griffin, go to green.
FBI! 趴下!
FBl! Get down!
- 一个也别动!  - 听到没!
-Nobody move!  -Clear!
长官, 没人
Sir, it's empty.
你听到FBI了, 兄弟, 他们不想付钱
You heard the FBl, bro. They're not gonna pay.
他们会付的, 否则我们会杀了菲尔兹和弗雷泽
They'll pay, or we'll kill Fields and Frazier.
让我们看看他们在 记者招待会上是怎么解释的
Let's see them explain that at their press conference.
- 你是怎么知道他们来了?  - 直升机
-How'd you know they'd come?  -Choppers.
每天两次他们飞来维加斯 做交通报告...
Twice a day they fly to Vegas to do traffic reports...
...但是后一架在高峰时间没来
...but that last one didn't come at rush hour.
我就知道是他们了
I knew it was them.
我说了, 蹲下!
I said, stay down!
格里芬, 500英尺内搜索 给我找出点有价值的东西
Griffin, secure a 500 -foot perimeter and get me something.
车轮痕迹, 做DNA分析的烟蒂 反正就是要有东西
Tire tracks, cigarette butts for DNA, but something.
是的, 长官
You got it, sir.
长官, 我接到奥肯探员的电话 哈特没有上飞机
Sir, I just got a call from Agent Okun. Hart didn't get on the plane.
我要和麦凯伦探员说话
I need a minute with Agent McCarren.
显然, 她冒充经痛在福勒探员的 协助下逃脱
Well, apparently, she faked a case of cramps and escaped with Fuller.
你的白痴男朋友在哪?
Where's your idiot boyfriend?
前男友! 当他离开他们的时候 是去给哈特买止血垫
Ex -boyfriend! He was on his way to buy tampons for her when he left with them.
哦, 多么, 多么体贴呀
Oh, well, how very, very considerate.
我没时间管这些了 她毁了我的计划
I don't have time for this. She is ruining my investigation!
她只是试图去找另一条线索, 沃尔特
She's just trying to get another bestseller out of this, Walter.
这应该是你的线索
This should be your bestseller.
你是对的
You're right.
我要找出她和福勒 然后以妨碍司法公正逮捕她们
I want you to find her and Fuller and arrest them for obstruction of justice.
我们在明处, 祖尔, 他们在哪? 有人要见我们
We're in the clear. Joel, where are they? Someone's gonna see us.
他们说他们需要为任务做准备
They said they had to get ready for the mission.
我们的时间快用完了
Well, we are running out of time.
拉维恩 考克斯(Laverne Cox)美国女影星
电视真人秀明星 电视制片人
出演《女子监狱》中的索菲亚(Sophia Burset)
雪莉-奇泽姆美国国会黑人女议员
帮助组建了全国黑人妇女政治大会
- 来吧, 拉维恩和雪莉, 快走!  - 准备好了吗?
-Come on, Laverne and Shirley, move it!  -Ready?
- 装备完全  - 很棒, 除了...
-Armed.  -And fabulous, except for the...
我们走, 杰夫, 你那到了警察局档案
Let's go. Jeff, you got the rap sheets.
是的, 这家伙...这家伙还在狱中
All right, this guy... This guy's still in prison.
折家伙太矮了和拍录像带的不符
This guy is too short to match the surveillance video.
这家伙...这家伙是这家伙的兄弟
This guy is... This guy's brothers with this guy.
入室行窃, 重大汽车盗窃
Burglary, grand theft auto.
停停, 我们怎么找到多莉 ?
Hold on. How are we supposed to get to Dolly?
我们去酒吧, 出示警徽然后审问她
We go to the drag club, flash our badges and interrogate her.
要是她不合作呢?
And if she doesn't cooperate?
暴力, 我会抓住她的
Violence. I have some catching up to do.
然后她会报警说被格雷西 哈特袭击了
Then she's gonna call the cops and say that she was attacked by Gracie Hart.
接着科林斯就找了来 然后我们就都进了大屋子
Then Collins is gonna find out about it, and we'll all end up in the big house.
- 我们被搅和了  - 别担心
-We gotta blend in.  -Not to worry.
我知道要做什么, 我等这一天 差不多都等了一辈子了
I know what to do. I've been waiting for this moment my entire life.
让我们再复习一遍, 我们知道发现和 审问了多莉帕顿才离开
Let's go over this again. We're not leaving until we find and interrogate Dolly Parton.
这是我从也没想到会说的话, 杰夫?
That's something I never thought I'd say. Jeff?
- 我是后援, 如果多莉 试图逃跑, 我就抓住她  - 我负责检查化妆间
-I'm backup. If Dolly tries to flee, I got her.  -I'm gonna check out the dressing rooms.
我只是来这里欢度快乐时光的
I'm really just here to have a good time.
哦, 上帝, 我都不明白 为什么我不是帝娜
Oh, God, I just don't see why I couldn't be Tina.
- 你不明白?  - 我是蒂娜特纳的粉丝
-You don't see that?  -I am the Tina Turner fan.
女士们, 停停, 我们是来找情报的 耳机准备好了吗?
Ladies, knock it off. We are here to get information. Earpieces in?
好的, 我们开始吧
All right, let's move.
- 我想要去那儿?  - 去后台?
-I wanna go in there.  -Go backstage?
丽莎二人组, 你们是下一个
Liza plus two, you're up next.
你好, 我是伊丽莎白泰勒 我们这来了谁?
Hello. I'm Elizabeth Taylor. What do we have here?
帝娜和...?
Tina and...?
- 珂珂  -你准备去哪儿
-Coco.  -Where do you think you're going?
唯一能去化妆间的 就是我们的正式演员...
The only people who get to go to the dressing rooms are our regulars...
...和那麦克风的 在他们演出结束之后
...and our open -mikers after they pass round one.
你能站在一边吗, 珂珂? 你是?
Could you step aside, Coco? And you are?
-她是优雅的, 她是可爱的 她是T型台上最好的
She's classy, she's lovely, she's perfect to a T.
我的最爱, 丽莎
My very favorite, Liza with a Z.
- 富尔曼  - 杰夫? 嗨, 我是珍妮特
-Foreman.  -Jeff? Hi, it's Janet.
我只是想让你和谈谈我们的事情
I just wanted to talk to you about us.
- 现在不是个好时间  - 背景是丽莎明尼里吗?
-Now's not a good time.  -Is that Liza Minnelli in the background?
是的, 在收音机上 我在家, 在听丽莎的歌
Yeah. On the radio. I'm just home, listening to Liza.
我不想那样结束
I don't want it to end this way.
我知道你对我很生气 但是我还是很在乎你...
I know that you're mad at me, but I still care about you...
- 找到了  - 如果有机会给我回个电话
-Got it.  -Just give me a call if you get a chance.
两个点, 科瓦尔和哈蒙
Two -block radius of Koval and Harmon.
丽莎明尼里, 我知道他在哪了, 我们走
Liza Minnelli. I know where he is. Let's move.
哦, 结束了, 明尼里小姐! 你将在下一场中再上场
Oh, you go, Miss Minnelli! You are definitely on to the next round.
你为什么不去后台休息一下
Why don't you go rest up backstage.
她是不是很棒?
Wasn't she wonderful?
坏消息, 我要要进化妆间就必须表演
Bad news. We want in those dressing rooms, we have to perform.
我不会出去像是男人要扮女人...
I am not going out there as a woman pretending to be a man...
...扮帝娜 特纳, 我不能承担这笔治疗费用
...pretending to be Tina Turner. I can't afford therapy on my salary.
我们还有其他的选择吗? 没! 没!
What other choice do we have? No! No!
你能做到的, 好嘛, 你能 因为你是萨姆福勒, 是FBI...
You can do this. Okay, you can because you are Sam Fuller, FBl...
...没有什么可以吓倒你, 我是格雷西 哈特...
...and nothing scares you. I am Gracie Hart...
...在这个时刻, 我也是大鸟 也没什么能吓倒我...
...and at this moment, I am also Big Bird, and nothing scares me...
...除了失去谢丽尔, 因为能有 像她那样的朋友, 有任何朋友, 对我...
...except losing Cheryl because having a friend like her, having any friend, for me...
都是很珍贵, 很珍贵的事情, 好吗?
...is a really, really rare thing, okay?
好的, 但是我不唱歌
Okay, but I am not singing.
...难以置信的蒂娜特纳!
...fabulous Tina Turner!
一切都会好起来的 只要像帝娜那样
Everything is gonna be okay. Just be Tina -ish.
- 你能扮帝娜  - 只要拿着
-You can do Tina.  -Just take it.
- 我不唱歌  - 只要拿着
-I am not singing.  -Just take it.
他怎么到我前面来了? 我是在他前面的!
How come he gets to go first? I was here before him!
在我的单子上就是这样的, 按字母顺序, 帝娜, 接着帝娜, 还是帝娜
It's all right here on my list, in alphabetical order. Tina, then Tina, then Tina.
你们怎么都唱一样的歌 那有什么区别? 开始
And you're all doing the same song anyway. What's the difference? Hit it.
微笑
Smile.
- 你笑了?  - 我在微笑
-You smiling?  -I am smiling.
来吧, 男孩们
Come on, boys!
拿起来, 丽莎!
Bring back Liza!
谢谢, 晚安
Thank you and good night.
不, 不, 我们必须待在这 待在这, 摇摆, 摇摆
No, no, we have to stay here. Stay here. Shake. Shake.
哦, 看着, 他会给我们钩子 唱吧, 帝娜
Oh, shoot. He's gonna give us the hook. Sell it, Tina.
扭
Rolling.
- 我找到了多莉 !  - 他说什么?
-I found Dolly!  -What's he saying?
所有的帝娜, 联合起来! 上场!
Tinas of the world, unite! Take the stage!
摇晃!
Shake!
我找到多莉 了 他在就把挑上了我...
I found Dolly. He picked me up at the bar...
...还邀请我去五号化妆间 我很高兴我穿了高跟鞋
...and invited me to dressing room five. I'm glad I wore the heels.
- 去五号化妆间找多莉   - 收到
-Joel found Dolly in dressing room five.  -Got it.
- 我们需要一个精彩的结束  - 也许我应该把我的帽子拿下来
-We need a big finish.  -Maybe I should take my top off.
不, 我们需要个漂亮的退场
No, we need a good big finish.
- 抱我起来  - 不
-Pick me up.  -No.
FBI, 抱我起来
FBl. Pick me up!
安静, 安静
Settle down, settle down.
- 微笑  - 我个人并不喜欢这...
-Smile!  -Well, I personally didn't love it...
...但是谁的喜爱才能决定一切?
...but what's love got to do with it?
观众才能决定, 让我们在今晚 畅饮吧
The crowd decides and tonight the drinks must be strong...
...因为帝娜在下场还要演出!
...because this Tina's moving on to the next round!
来吧, 来吧!
Come on, come on!
他说五号化妆间
All right, he said dressing room number five.
就在那边, 祖尔, 让我们来搞定
It's that one right there. Joel, let us handle this.
- 他邀请了我  - 我会给你他的电话号码的
-He invited me!  -I'll get you his phone number.
你好? 我能帮你们什么吗?
Hello? Can I help you boys?
你知道关于美国小姐被绑架的事情吗?
What do you know about the Miss United States kidnapping?
汤姆阿伯纳西, 豪华轿车司机
Tom Abernathy, the limo driver.
你付了他200美元, 让他把车停在远离 老年之家的门口, 为什么?
You paid him 200 bucks to park far away from the entrance to the senior home. Why?
我不知道你在说什么 请离开
I don't know what you're talking about. Please leave.
你知道, 通常我能冷静地审问你 但是我现在赶时间
You know, normally I would calmly interrogate you, but I'm kind of in a rush.
- 我什么也不知道  - 说!
-I don't know anything!  -Talk!
- 不, 别! 不是我, 是其他人  - 什么人?
-No, please! It wasn't me. It was some guy.  -What guy?
当我在宝藏岛做赌博姑娘的时候遇见他的
I met him when I was a keno girl at Treasure Island.
我从他那借钱了, 但是还不出来
I borrowed money from him and couldn't pay it back.
- 他说他将...  - 他叫什么名字?!
-He said he would dump...  -What was his name?!
肯? 凯尔? 卡尔? 我记不得了 他没有告诉我他的姓
Ken? Cal? Karl? I don't remember. He didn't tell me his last name.
卡尔
Karl.
- 卡尔斯蒂尔在那份名单上  - 他是兄弟之一
-Karl Steele was on that sheet.  -One of the brothers.
路易和卡尔斯蒂尔, 入室行窃 重大汽车盗窃, 你在宝藏岛遇见他
Lou and Karl Steele, armed robbery, grand theft auto. You met him at Treasure Island.
- 我们走  - 去哪?
-Let's go.  -Where are we going?
宝藏岛, 他们就在那
Treasure Island, that's where they took them.
- 你怎么知道?  - 多莉 说斯蒂尔兄弟以前是海岛
-How do you know?  -Dolly said the Steele brothers were pirates.
珍妮特带着后援来了
Janet is here with backup.
报告, 珍妮特来了
I repeat, Janet is here.
杰夫?
Jeff?
- 她在哪?  - 谁在哪?
-Where is she?  -Where is who?
- 你是个恶心的说谎者, 杰夫  - 是的
-You are a lousy liar, Jeff.  -Yeah.
你是个优秀的说谎者
And you're a good one.
- 我们怎么离开这?  - 我不知道, 但是这需要计谋
-How are we gonna get out of here?  -I don't know, but it has to be subtle.
宝藏岛
女士们先生们, 下个表演 将在20分钟之后开始
Ladies and gentlemen, the next show will be in 20 minutes.
好的, 我们走
Okay, let's go.
你们两个闭嘴, 否则就去死
You both keep your mouths shut, or you're dead.
斯蒂尔兄弟会参加宝藏岛表演
The Steele brothers were fired from the Treasure Island show.
谢丽尔说了她的赃物在危险之中
Cheryl said something about her booty being on the line.
谢丽尔 从不会提到她的屁股称作赃物或者提到她的屁股, 以前
Cheryl would never refer to her ass as a booty or refer to her ass, period.
她叫它波 -波
She calls it a po -po.
- 抱歉! 抱歉! 抱歉!  - 抱歉!
-Excuse me! Excuse me!  -Excuse us!
- FBI需要你的车  - 那不可能!
-FBl. We need your car.  -Well, that's not gonna happen.
滚开, 嗨!
Get lost. Hey!
哈特, 哈特! 太多了!
Hart, Hart! Too much!
是的, 我知道, 但是现在 我有几分知道你为什么这么喜欢这样了
Yeah, I know, but now I kind of see why you enjoy it so much.
你是好市民. 你可以拿回你的车 非常感谢
You are fine citizens, and you will get your car back. Thank you very much.
- 好的  - 我们这就来了
-All right.  -Okay, here I come.
- 我很抱歉我要转身  - 好的
-I'm sorry. I'm gonna turn.  -Okay.
抱歉, 抱歉, 祖尔做了什么 把这个东西焊在了...?
Sorry, sorry. What did Joel do, weld this thing on...?
保持安静, 按照我说的做 这样就没人会受伤
Just keep quiet, do as you're told and nobody gets hurt.
我相信他, 你不相信他吗, 谢丽尔?
I believe him. Don't you believe him, Cheryl?
- 他对这种事情是不会撒谎的 - 你能闭嘴嘛?!
-He wouldn't lie about a thing like that.  -Will you just shut up?!
杰夫
Jeff.
杰夫! 格雷西和山姆去...
Jeff! Gracie and Sam went to...
继续, 如果你不想 在监狱里待上几年的话...
Go on, if you don't wanna spend a few years in prison...
...因为妨碍司法公正
...for obstruction of justice.
哪个监狱?
Which prison?
为了以防我没机会说...
Just in case I don't get a chance to say it...
我很抱歉说了关于马休斯的事情
...I'm sorry for getting on you about that whole Matthews thing.
这不是我的本意
It was none of my business.
那没什么
That's all right.
我把他吓跑了
I scared him off.
但是事实是, 对嘛 他回来救我
But the thing is, right, he came back to save me.
我的意思是, 为什么某人会回来 救某人, 如果他们没有...
I mean, why would somebody come back to save someone if they didn't have...
...感觉的话? 你知道吗?
...feelings? You know?
我肯定他喜欢你, 也许他只是去工作了
I'm sure he liked you, but maybe he was just doing his job.
也许
Maybe.
男人, 不能依赖他们, 你不能...
Men. Can't live with them, you can't....
- 不, 这就是了  - 是的
-No, that's about it.  -Yep.
好的, 继续
Okay, hold on.
来吧!
Come on!
- 好的! 很清楚那没用  - 别说我, 帝娜
-Okay! Clearly that's not working.  -Don't start with me, Tina.
我们会死吗?
Are we gonna die?
如果你能在接下来的五分钟内 长出腮的话就不会
Not if you develop gills in the next five minutes.
让我们回到娱乐场
Let's go back through the casino.
好吧, 我走这边, 你走...
Okay. I'm gonna take this side, you take that...
斯蒂尔兄弟
The Steele brothers.
路易! 路易和卡尔斯蒂尔兄弟, 别动! FBI! 别动! 别动!
Lou! Lou and Karl Steele, freeze! FBl! Freeze! Freeze!
- 跑  - 跑, 跑, 跑
-Keep going.  -Move. Move, move.
嗨, 嗨!
Hey, hey!
四部需要人手帮忙
We're gonna need more help in sector four.
谢丽尔和斯坦在哪里?
Where are Cheryl and Stan?
- 哪?  - 你压碎了我的手腕
-Where?  -You're breaking my wrist.
- 谢丽尔和斯坦在哪里?  - 他们在船底
-Where are Cheryl and Stan?  -They're at the bottom of the boat.
哪艘船?!
What boat?!
路易!
Lou!
我来了, 兄弟!
I'm coming, bro!
- 我来处理  - 不, 不, 我来处理, 你去找谢丽尔
-I got your back.  -No, no. I got this. You go for Cheryl.
- 你确定?  - 我能搞定!
-You sure?  -I've got this!
二十美元赌这对姐妹赢
Twenty dollars on the sister.
你很好, 我会好好享受的
You're good. I'm gonna enjoy this.
- 女士没什么好说的了  - 我不想说, 我想唱歌!
-Nothing left to talk about, lady.  -I'm not gonna talk. I'm gonna sing!
但愿你没打算要孩子
Hope you weren't planning on reproducing.
- 我来了! 我来了!  - 格雷西!
-I'm coming! I'm coming!  -Gracie!
一切都会好起来的
Everything's gonna be okay.
- 我解下你, 你会游泳吗?  - 我会游吗?
-I've got you. Can you swim?  -Can I swim?
我在孟达库露营地是初级救生员 我还是迷你高尔夫的冠军
I made junior lifesaver at Camp Mondago. I was captain of the miniature golf team.
- 斯坦, 快游! 快游!  - 谢丽尔还没好
-Stan, just go! Go, go!  -Not without Cheryl!
- 斯坦, 我来救她, 你快游! 游!  - 好的
-Stan, I have her! Go! Go!  -Okay.
- 哪里?  - 后面被封死了
-Where?  -The back is blocked.
- 游到最近的舷窗, 就在那  - 哦, 好的
-Go to the nearest porthole. Right here.  -Oh, okay.
舷窗上有大炮!
There's a cannon in my porthole!
- 拉! 使劲, 快!  - 我的上帝!
-Pull! Come on, hurry!  -My God!
它动了
It's moving!
- 走!  - 我就走, 我就走
-Go!  -Here I go. Here I go.
格雷西!
Gracie!
哈特在几分钟前跳下去了
Hart jumped in a few minutes ago.
- 奥肯, 黑尔斯, 救他!  - 我不会游泳, 长官
-Okun, Hills, help him!  -I can't swim, sir.
我命令你
I gave you an order.
格雷西...
Gracie...
- 美国小姐  - 你可以叫我谢丽尔
-Miss United States.  -You can call me Cheryl.
没事了, 我们接住你了, 我们接住你了
It's okay, we got you. We got you.
所以我们所有的线索...
And so all of our clues...
...最终引导我们来到这儿, 她来了
...eventually led us here. Here she is.
- 干得好, 哈特  - 谢谢, 长官
-Nice work, Hart.  -Thank you, sir.
- 为你在我们的团队而骄傲  - 那太好了
-Proud to have you on our team.  -That's great.
- 非常感谢  - 哦, 你一定是在开玩笑
-Thank you very much.  -Oh, you've gotta be kidding.
你威胁要把她扔进监狱的
You threatened to throw her in jail.
跪下来谢谢她解决了 你不能解决的犯罪
Get on your knees and thank her for solving a crime you couldn't solve.
- 把你的假意的握手放在...  - 好的, 先生, 站在一边去吧
-Take your little handshake and put it...  -Okay, Mr. Living -on -the -Edge.
我们都在一个团队, 没事
We're all on the same team. It's all right.
好吧, 我想他不会让记者久等的
Well, I guess he doesn't wanna keep the press waiting.
格雷西!
Gracie!
哦, 你一定很累了, 为了就我
Oh, you must be getting really tired of saving my life.
不, 不, 那是很好的经历 哦, 谢谢你关于"booty"的暗语
No, no, it's good exercise. Oh, and thank you for the "booty" tip.
我真的很不说服说这个 但是情况紧急
I felt so uncomfortable saying it, but it was an emergency.
- 我也知道你会听懂得  - 是的, 朋友是做什么的, 对吗?
-And I knew you'd be listening.  -Yeah, well, what are friends for, right?
哦, 说到朋友, 我要介绍你 认识杰夫 富尔曼先生
Oh, and speaking of friends, I would like to introduce you to Mr. Jeff Foreman.
哦, 我们刚才见过了, 他是游泳健将
Oh, we already met. He's a wonderful swimmer.
你很有浮力的
Well, you're so buoyant.
好吧, 过来这, 我要和你说会
Okay. Come here. I gotta talk to you for a second.
只是一些忠告
Just a couple words of advice.
别提出波科诺斯, 至少开始的几个月
Don't bring up the Poconos, at least for a couple of months.
好的
Okay.
现在过去他那吧
Now go get him.
格雷西, 我为你自豪
Gracie, I'm so proud of you.
哦, 谢谢
Oh, thank you.
你知道嘛, 甚至没有饰品和光泽 和我所有的魔法...
And, you know, even without the makeup and the gloss and all my magic...
...你现在看上去是从未有过的美
...you've never looked more beautiful than you do now.
你也是
Neither have you.
- 哦, 谢谢  - 格雷西
-Oh, thank you.  -Gracie.
- 噢, 斯坦  - 我很抱歉
-Oh, Stan.  -I'm so sorry.
- 没事, 斯坦  - 这都是我的错
-It's okay, Stan.  -This was all my fault.
- 我有这个缺点...  - 赌博, 我和你妈妈谈过了
-I have this weakness for...  -For gambling. I talked to your mother.
- 你和我妈妈谈了?  - 是的
-You talked to my mother?  -Yeah.
- 她是不是还在想要她的600美元?  - 是的, 她想要你还她
-Does she want her 600 back?  -Yeah, she wants that back.
但是她很为你自豪
But she's very proud of you.
你只要远离荡妇... 老虎机一段时间, 好吗?
You just need to stay away from the sluts... The slots for a little while. Okay? Okay.
我们走
Let's go.
- 这边, 长官  - 你为什么这么做
-Over here, sir.  -Why'd you do it?
你觉得怎样?
How you doing?
- 很好, 你呢?  - 也不赖
-Good. You?  -Good.
嗨, 你在那边踢了某人的屁股
Hey, you kicked some po -po out there.
- 谢谢, 你也是  - 谢谢
-Thanks. You too.  -Thank you.
谢谢...
And thanks....
谢谢你后来赶过来帮我
Thanks for coming back for me.
- 这不代表我爱你或者其他什么  - 我知道
-It's not like I love you or anything.  -I know.
- 我只是做我的工作  - 我知道
-I was just doing my job.  -I know.
但是我得承认...
But I gotta admit...
...当你说没有朋友的时候...
...when you were saying that stuff back there about not having any friends...
...我知道你的感觉
...l know what you mean by that.
你有朋友
You got a friend.
是的
Yeah.
吉森探员, 那个邮件欺诈的?
Agent Johnson, over in Mail Fraud?
我想他喜欢你
I think he likes you.
是的
Yeah.
不, 但是如果, 你知道... 那不起作用的话, 然后...
No, but if, you know.... If that doesn't work out, then...
...你还有朋友
...you always got:
你们知道吗? 她就在那, 你们能和她说话
You know what? She's right down there. You can talk to her.
哈特女士! 哈特女士!
Ms. Hart! Ms. Hart!
这会写进你的下一本书吗?
Is this going in your next book?
伙计们, 伙计们, 我有两件事要说
Guys, guys. I have two things to say.
第一, 不会有下本书, 第二...
First of all, there's not gonna be a next book. Second....
没有评论, 再次
No comment. Ever again. Ever.
谢谢, 谢谢, 不要听, 不要听
Thank you, thank you. Not listening. Not listening.
科林斯先生, 描述一下我们的调查, 长官
Mr. Collins, characterize the investigation for us, sir.
我从不放弃, 因为"放弃" 不存在在我的字典里
I never gave up because the word "quit" is not in my vocabulary.
也没有"失败"...
Neither is "failure," "A for effort," "abandon ship"...
这就是我们纽约的做法
And that is how we do it in New York.
好的, 听着, 改变一下安排计划吧
Okay, listen up. Got a change in the assignment schedule.
哈特和福勒成了搭档
Hart's gonna be partnering with Fuller.
市长的预防青少年犯罪的项目开始了
And the mayor's youth -crime prevention program is back on.
- 指挥官想要...  - 你是我的新拍档
-The director wants....  -You're my new partner.
你必须喜欢我, 如果某人 向我开枪, 你要来就我
You have to like me. And back me up if someone's shooting at me.
没必要
Not necessarily.
- 你要些吗?  - 我们工作吧, 注意提高你的警惕
-Want some?  -Let's get to work. Keep your heads up.
我们现在是拍档了, 但是有些事情 我还是喜欢自己处理
We're partners now, but there's something I need to take care of alone.
- 你确信你不想要后援?  - 这是单独行动
-Are you sure you don't need backup?  -This is solo.
- 我们很酷?  - 酷
-So we cool?  -Cool.
好的, 我走了
All right, I'm gonna roll.
嗨
Hi.
很抱歉打断了, 我是FBI的格雷西 哈特...
I'm sorry to interrupt. I'm Gracie Hart of the FBl...
...我们得到消息 普丽西拉写了一份关于我的读书报告...
...and our information indicated that a Priscilla was doing a book report on me...
...所以我想来看看我是否能帮上忙
...so I thought I would come by and see if I could be of any assistance.
哦, 上帝
Oh, my God.
嗨, 普丽西拉
Hey, Priscilla.
好的, 我想我们直接跳过开始上英语课...
Well, I suppose we can skip ahead to English...
...让普丽西拉把报告给我们尊敬的客人
...and let Priscilla give her report in honor of our guest.
把我们的数学书放下
Let's put our math books away.
- 嗨  - 谢谢你能来
-Hi.  -Thanks for coming.
由于我们在教室...
Since we're in class...
...我想要告诉你一些我最近学到的事情
...l would like to share with you something I learned recently.
一个小小的教训, 那就是...
A little lesson, which is...
...人们可能会在乎在乎自己的人...
...people may care about people who care about themselves...
...但是我不在乎那些人
...but I just don't really care about those people.
- 不是很明白你说的?  - 不?
-Not really following you.  -No?
来这儿
Come here.
我们必须要放下这
We'll just have to take this.
还有这些
And then we'll take those.
然后我们就...
And then we'll just....
这就是你
There you are.
现在做你的读书报告
Now go do your book report.
孩子们! 安静!
Kids! Quiet!
嗨, 嗨, 嗨, 先插个内容, 好的...
Hey, hey, hey, put a lid on it, all right...
...我想要给大家点东西, 好吗?
...or I'm gonna have to rough you guys up a little bit, okay?
小姐 哈特?
Miss Hart?
你必须承认战争不是最终答案
Until you admit that fighting is never the answer. Ever.
因为我们真的需要什么?
Because what do we really want?
谁知道?
Anyone?
没人? 没人知道?
Nobody? Nobody knows?
普丽西拉, 我们需要什么?
Priscilla, what do we want?
世界和平
World peace.
那么坚持你们的信念...
And the strength to hold fast to your beliefs...
...当社会迫使你去适应游戏规则的时候 知道我说什么吗?
...while society's forcing you to conform to a Barbie -doll image, know what I'm saying?
你们不明白我说的吗? 好的...
You don't know what I'm saying? Okay, well...
...这大部分...
...it's mostly....
这就是世界和平
It's mostly world peace.
在录像带上, 你注意到绑匪试图 绑架斯坦费尔特...
On the video, you noticed the assailants were attempting to abduct Stan Fields...
...你开始追查"furder"...Fur, 好吧
...and you pursued the matter "furder"... Fur... Okay.
一些储蓄公债, 和1901
Some savings bonds and a 1 901 ...
不, 这不那么老. 是2001...
No, it's not quite that old. It's a 2001 ....
你是那个...
You're the one...
该死的线!
Damn that line!
祖尔提出这个非常...
Joel has come up with this very...
镇静?
Sedate?
是的, 就说这, 是的
Yeah, say it, yeah.
富尔曼!
Foreman!
- 看, 我能处理好胸部?  - 你们的?
-Watch it. I'm handling breasts here.  -Yours?
你追查线索"furder"..., 进一步...
You pursued the matter furder... Further...
- “Furder”  - “furder”?
-'Furder.'  -"Furder"?
- 不会发生  - 我们还有什么其他选择?
-Not gonna happen.  -What other choice do we have?
在绑架录像带上, 你发现...
On the kidnapping video, you noticed that the...
你知道说什么, 杰夫
You know what to say, Jeff.
- 你叫什么名字?  - 富尔曼
-What's your name?  -Foreman.
富尔曼? 好的
Foreman? Okay.
毛球
Fur ball.
武力巾帼
特工佳丽
选美俏卧底
- 前进一些  - 后退, 后退, 后退
-Little further.  -Back up, back up, back up.
感觉...我不舒服...
Feel... I'm upset...
你是谁? 我是...? 我在这干什么?
Who are you? What am...? What am I doing here?
斯坦
Stan
Stan.
不要松开我, 我还有15分钟
Don't untie me. I have another 15 minutes.
你提到了早餐?
You mentioned something about breakfast?
- 非专业的  - 保持扭动
-Unprofessional.  -Still rolling.
- 哦, 我的...  - 兄弟! 你的面具!
-Oh, my...  -Bro! Your mask!
我们需要一些齿科动物, 松鼠, 袋熊
We need a bunch of rodents. Squirrels, wombats.
- 我能跟吗?  - 是的, 是的
-Can I go back to the trailer?  -Yeah, yeah.
- 你喜欢海盗, 你想要亲他  - 闭嘴!
-You like the pirate. You wanna kiss him.  -Shut up!